<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <row>
    <OCLC>1386890</OCLC>
    <TITLE>An American Dictionary of the English language, &c. With an Introductory Discourse on the Languages of Western Asia and Europe, and a Concise Grammar of the English language. By   Noah Nebster, LL.D. 2 vols.  New York. 1828.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC>5291825</OCLC>
    <TITLE>A Course of Lectures on Natural (Philosophy and the Mechanical Arts. By Thomas Young, M.D. F.R.S. &c. Plates. 2 vols. London. 1807.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Quæstiones Philosophicæ in justi systematis ordinem dispositae; Auctoribus adductis, et singulis in proprias hypotheses dispertitis. Cum appendice de Legibus Disputandi. Operâ Tho. Johnson, A. M., &c.  Cantabrigiæ. 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Illustrations of Paley’s Natural Theology. With Descriptive Let- ter Press. By James Paxton. Many plates.  Boston, 1827.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Journals of the House of Representatives of the United States, 1st and 2d Session, 19th Congress, 1825—6, and 1826—7. 2 vols. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Report of the Committee of the House of Representatives of the United States, 1st Session, 19th Congress, 1825—6. 2 vols. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ditto, do, 2d Session, 19th Congress, 1826—7. 3 vols. Do.  State Papers, 1st Session, 19th Congress, 1825—6. 10 vols. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ditto, 2d Session, 19th Congress, 1826—7. 10 vols. Do.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Journals of the Senate of the United States, 1825—6, and 1826—7. 2 vols. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Documents printed by order of the Senate of the United States, 1st Session, 19th Congress, 1825—6, and 1826—7. 5 vols. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ditto, 2nd Session, 19th Congress, 1826—7. 3 vols. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Acontius, 56, D. Statagematum Satanae libri octo. Jacobo Acontio, Authore. Amstelædami, 1664.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Allen, 115—1, F. Certain Select Discourses on the Doctrine of the Two Covenants, &c. and on Faith and Justification. By William Allen. London, 1699.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Alstedius, 115, Q. Theologia Scholastica didactica, exhibens locos communes Theologicos methodo scholastica, quatuor in. partes tributa, studio Johannis-Henrici Alstedii. Hanoviae, 1618</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Altenstaig, 50, Q. Lexicon Theologicum quo omnium fere terminorum et obscuriorum vocum etymologiae, ambiguitates,  definitiones, usus, enucleatae ob oculos ponuntur, et dilucide explicantur. Post summum laborem Joannis Altenstaig, S. T. D. &c. Studio et labore R. D. Joannis Tytz. Coloniae Agrippinae, 1619.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ambrose 131, F. Media: the Middle Things, in reference to the first and last Things; or the Means, Duties, Ordinances, both secret, private, and publick, for continuance and intrease of a Godly Life, (once begun) tell we come to  Heaven, &c &c. &c. By Isaac Ambrose. London, 1674.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aschenbrenner, 143—6, Q. De Episcopo in Ecclesia, et Ecclesia in Episcopo, &c. &c. &c. Auct. D. P. Aschenbrenner. Bambergæ, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barclay, 9, Q. An Apology for the true Christian Divinity; being an Explanation and Vindication of the Principles and Doctrines of the people called Quakers. By Robert Barclay. Birmingham, 1765. [Presented by David Barclay, son of the author.] </TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bates, 258, O. The Harmony of the Divine Attributes, in the contrivance and accomplishment of Man’s Redemption by the Lord Jesus Christ. By William Bates, D. D. London, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bauer, 91—2, Q. Theses ex Theologia Universa, cum Dissertatione de Exceptionibus contra SS. Oecum. Concilii Tridentini authoritatem factis, &c. &c. Auct. Chr. P. Fred. Bauer ab Heppenstein. Bambergæ, 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Baumann, 142—5, Q. De Angelorum et Hominum primo principio et ultimo fine, dc. &c. Auct. D. J. F. Baumann. Bambergæ, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Berriman, 151, D. Christian Doctrines and Duties explained and recommended; in forty Sermons. By William Berriman, D. D. late Rector of St. Andrew’s, Undershaft, &c. 2 vols. London, 1751.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Berriman, 152, O. A Original Dissertation upon 1 Tim. iii. 16.— Wherein Rules are laid down to distinguish, in various readings, which is genuine; an account is given of above a hundred Greek MSS. of St. Paul’s Epistles, &c. &c. and the common reading of that text, GOD was manifest in the Flesh, is proved to be the true one, &c. &c. &c. By John Berriman, M. A. &c. London, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Berriman, 170, O. The Gradual revelation of the Gospel; from the time of Man’s Apostacy. Set forth and explained in twenty-four Sermons, preached at the Lecture founded by the Hon Robert Boyle, Esq. in 1730, 1731 and 1732. By William Berriman, D. D. &c. 2 vols. London, 1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Besse, 111, F. A Collection of the Sufferings of the People called Quakers, for the Testimony of a Good Conscience, fromthe time of their being first distinguished by that name in 1650, to the time of the Act of Toleration in 1689.   Taken from original records, &c. by Joseph Besse. 2 vols. London, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bible, 4, F. The Holy Bible. Imp. folio. With engravings.— Ruled with red lines. 2 vols. Printed by Baskett, Oxford, 1717.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bible Society, 46, O. The third, sixth, seventh, sighth, ninth, tenth, eleventh, twelfth, fourteenth and fifteenth Reports of the British and Foreign Bible Society, with Appendices, &c.&c. London, 1807—1819.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Biblia, 55, D. Sacra Biblia cum augusto apparatu suo, scil. Chronol. Theol. Histor. et Geographico in angustum contracta. Bambergæ, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Biblia, 75, F. Divinae Scripturae, Veteris ac Novi Testamenti, omnia, Graecè. Curâ Philippi Melanchthon. Basileae, 1545.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Biblia, 78, Q. Testamenti Veteris et Novi Biblia Sacra ex Hebraeo et Græco Latina facta. Altera Tralatio Vetus est, Altera Nova cum adnotationibus Francisci Vatabli, prout utramq; Regio privilagio ornatum Rob Stephanus anno MDXLV. Lutetiae edidit, &c.&c. Hanoviae, 1605.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Biblia, 81, F. Biblia Sacra, Latinè. Curâ And. Osiandri, S. T. D. &c. Francofurti, 1611.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Blackwall, 169, O. The sacred Classics defended and illustrated; or, an Essay humbly offered towards proving the Purity, Propriety and True Eloquence of the Writers of the New Testament. By A. Blackwall, A. M. 2 vols. London, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bœttinger, 144—2, Q. Dissertationes ex universæ Theologiæ quadriennali Studio, &c. &c. Auct. G. C. E. Böttinger. Bambergæ, 1706.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bray, 115—2, F. Discourses on the Covenant of Grace, &c. being  Catechetical Lectures on the preliminary Questions and  Answers of the Church Catechism. — Three Catechetical Lectures on Faith and Justification. By Thomas Bray, D. D. London, 1699.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Burnet, 108, F. The history of the Reformation of the Church of England. By Gilbert Burnet. 3 vols. Dublin, 1730—1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bynaeus, 132, Q. Antonii Bynaei de Morte Jesu Christi. Cum figuris. Tom. 3. Amstelædami, 1691—1698.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Calmet, 25, F. Dictionnaire historique, critique, chronologique, geographique et litteral de la Bible, enrichi d&apos;un grand nombre de figures en taille douce qui représentent les Antiquitez Judaïques. Avec le Supplement. Par le. R. P. Dom Augustin Calmet. 4 tom. A Paris, 1722—1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Campbell, 27, Q. The Four Gospels translated from the Greek. With preliminary Dissertations, and Notes critical and explanatory. By George Campbell, D. D. &c Philadelphia, 1790.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cariath-sepher, 123—5, Q. Carieth-sepher, sive interpretante Oraculo biblico Josue XV. et Judicum 1. &c. &c. &c. Bambergae, 1735</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carranzani, 285, O. Summa omnium Conciliorum et Pontificum, collecta per F. Barth. Carranzani. Accesserunt Statuta quaedam Synodalia Paris. and Senon. Ecclesiae. Appexdix Conciliorum Galliæ, &c. &c. Cum Notis Fr. Sylvii, &c. & c. Parisiis, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catholic question, 50—1, O. Letters to the Roman Catholics of Philadelphia, and the United States of America. By a Friend, &c. Nos. 1 & 2. Philadelphia, 1822.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catholic questions, 50—3, O. address of the lay Trustees to the Congregation of St. Mary’s Church, on the subject of the approaching Election. Philadelphia, 1822.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chandler. 98, O. Sermons on various Subjects. By the late Rev. Samuel Chandler, D. D. &c. 3 vols. London, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chemnitius, 73, F. Harmonia Quatuor Evangelistorum, a Theologis celeberrimis D. Martino Chemnitio inchoata, D. Polycarpo Lysero continuata, et D. Johanne Gerhardo absoluta. Tom. 2. Francofurti, 1652</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chillingworth, 78, F. The Works of William Chillingworth, M. A. London, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chrysostomus, 74, F. S. Joannis Chrysostomi, Archiepiscopi Opera omnia quae exstant. Græcè. Curâ, Studio et Labore Henrici Savilii, Eq. Tom. 8. Etonae, 1612.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clarkson 44, O. A Portraiture of Quakerism. Taken from a View of the Education and Discipline, Social Manners, Civil and Political Economy, Religious Principles and Character of the Society of Friends. By Thomas Clarkson, M. A. &c. 3 vols. New York, 1806.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Claubergius, 348, O. Johannis Claubergii, S. T. D. &c. de Cognitione Dei et Nostri, quatenus naturali rationis lumine, secundum veram Philosophiam potest comparari, Exercitationes Centum. Franequerae, 1685.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Conwell, 50—5, O. Pastoral Charges, delivered by the Rt. Rev. Bishop Henry (Conwell,) Nov. 2, 1820 and Feb. 11, 1821. Philadelphia.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cotelerius, 35, F. SS. Patrum qui Temporibus Apostolicis floruerunt, Barnabæ, Clementis, Hermæ, Ignatii, Polycarpi, Opera edita et inedita, vera et supposititia; una cum Clementis, Ignatii, Polycarpi, Actis atque Martyriis. J. B. Cotelerius, Soc. Sorb. Theol. ex MSS. Codicibus eruit, ac correxit, Versionibusque et Notis illustravit. Cum Notis integris aliorum virorum doctorum, qui in singulos Patres memoratos scripserunt; item, Guilielmi Beveregii Codex Canonum primitivæ Ecclesiae vindicatus, Jacobi Usserii Dissertationes Ignatianæ, et Joan. Pearsonii Vindiciæ Epistolarum S. Ignatii. Recensuit et Notas aliquot adspersit Joannes Clericus. 2 tom. Antverpiæ, 1700.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cowherd, 21, Q. Facts Authentic, in Science and Religion: designed to illustrate a New Translation of the Bible. By the Rev. William Cowherd. 2 vols. Manchester, 1818—1820. [Presented by John T. Freeland.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Crawford, 1, D. An Essay on the Propagation of the Gospel; in which there are numerous facts and arguments adduced to prove that the Indians in America are descended from the Ten Tribes. By Charles Crawford, Esq. Philadelphia, 1801. [Presented by the Author.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cudworth, 30, Q. The True Intellectual System of the Universe: Wherein all the Reason and Philosophy of Atheism is confuted, and its Impossibility demonstrated. With a Discourse concerning the True Notion of the Lord’s Supper; and Two Sermons on John ii. 3, 4, and I. Cor. xv. 57. By Ralph Cudworth, D. D. With an account of his Life, Writings, &c. &c. by Thomas Birch, M. A. and F. R. S. 2 vols. London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>De-Rossi, 4, Q. Variæ Lectiones Veteris Testamenti ex immensa MSS. Editorumque Codicum Congerie haustæ et ad Samar. Textum, ad Vetustiss. Versiones, ad Accuratiores sacræ Criticæ Fontes ac Leges examinatae opera ac studio Johannis Bern. De-Rossi, S. T. D. &c. Volumina II, III et IV. Parmæ, 1785—1789.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Disciplina, 146—2, Q. Cum Deo Nexum, quem disciplinae philosophica inter se habent, arctissimun, &c. &c. &c. Lipsiæ, 1715.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Doddridge, 65, Q. A Course of Lectures on the Principal Subjects in Pneumatology, Ethics and Divinity: with references to the most considerable authors on each Subject. By Philip Doddridge, D. D. London, 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 256, O. Des. Erasmi Rotterodami Ecclesiastes, sive Concionator Evangelicus. Cum Dissertatione præliminari, &c. Londini, 1730.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Flacius, 86, F. Clavis Scripturæ Sacræ, hoc est, de Sermone Sacrarum Literarum recte cognoscendo. Auctore Matthia Flacio Illyrico. Curà Theodori Suiceri. Lipsiæe, 1695.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Fox, 114, F. A Journal or Historical Account of the Life, Travels, Sufferings, Christian Experiences and Labour of Love, in the Work of the Ministry, of that ancient, eminent and faithful servant of Jesus Christ, George Fox. London, 1765.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Franzius, 315, 0. Historia Animalium Sacra, in qua plerorumque Animalium praecipue Proprietates, &c. &c. ad usum iconologicum accommodantur. A Wolfgango Franzio, S.T. D. Wittenbergæ, 1621.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Frey, 121—8, Q. Theses ex Theologia exegetica, dogmatica, morali, nec non ex historia ecclesiastica, &c. &c. auct. F.A. Frey. Bambergæ, 1788.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Geist, 110—11, Q. Dissertatio philologico-critico-exegetica de carnis Resurrectione, ex Job. Cap. XIX. 25—27. Auct. P. C. Geist. Bambergæ, 1790.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Geuss, 110—5, Q. De Religione Christiana: auct. G. Geuss. Bambergæ, 1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Giroust, 357, 0. Les faux Pretextes du Pecheur,  ou le Pecheur  sans excuse. Avent prêché par le R. P. Giroust de la compagnie de Jesus. Tom. II. A Bruselle, 1707.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grindal, 120, F. The Historv of the Life and Acts of the most Rev. Father in God, Edmund Grindal, the first Bishop of London, and the second Archbishop of York and Canterbury, successively, in the Reign of Queen Elizabeth.   Describing the state of his time, &c. &c. &c. With an Appendix of Original  Religion and of the Church in MSS. &c. Portrait. London, 1710.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grotius, 11, D. Hugo Grotius de Veritate Religionis Christianæe: cum Notulis JoannisClerici. Accedunt ejusdem, de eligenda inter Christianos dissentientes Sententia, et contra Indifferentiam Religionum, libri duo. Glasguæ,  1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grotius, 37, F. Hugonis Grotii Opera omnia Theologica. Londini. 1679. Item, Ejusdem Epistola quotquot reperiri potuerunt. 4 tom. in 5. Amstelodami, 1687.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grotius, 89, Q. Hugonis Grotii Annotationes in Vetus et Novum Testamentum juxta Editionem Amstelædamensem, MDCLXXIX, in compendium redacta, quibus nova  in accedit Præfatio, a Samuele Moody, A. M. &c. 2 tom. 1. Londini, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hammond, 294, O. A Practical Catechism. By H. Hammond, D. D. Whereunto is added, the Reasonableness of Christian Religion. By the same Author. London, 1662.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hare, 176, O. Psalmorum Liber, in Versiculos metrice divisus, &c. &c. Cum Dissertatione de antiqua Hebraeorum Poesi, &c. Accedunt Poescos Hebraicae Specimina, &e.  Edidit Franciscus Hare, S. T. P. Episc. Cicestr. Hebraicè et Latinè. Tom. 2. Londini, 1736.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Harold, 50—4, O. A Letter to the Rev. W. V. Harold on reading his late Reply to a “Catholic Layman.” By an admirer of Fenelon. Philadelphia, 1822</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hartman, 144—4, Q. Allegata et Probata Philosophiae Christianae, &c. &c. Auct. P. C. Hartman. Duderstadii, 1690.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Haven, 103, Q. Petri V. Haven M. Ph. Commentatio analytica  in Epistolam Pauli ad Titum; cum Praefatione Sig. J. Baumgarten. Halæ Magdeburgicæ, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heckel, 120—4, Q. De Patriarchis Commentatio historico-critico-canonia, &c. Auct. P.P. Heckel et P. S. Schlicker. Bambergæ, 1792.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heinaichen, 110—4, Q. Concordia Vulgatae Latinæ cum Fonte  Hebraico, &c. &c Auct. F. E. Heinaichen. Wirceburgi, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hermann 110—3, Q. Unio Religionis Protestanticae cum Catholica, &c. &c Auct. F. G. Hermann. Augustae Vindel. 177</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Herring, 96, O. Seven Sermons on Public Occasions. By the  most Rev. Dr. Thomas Herring, late Archbishop of Canterbury, &c. Dublin, 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hervey, 12, D. Theron and Aspasio: or, a series of Dialogues and Letters, upon the most important and interesting Subjects. By James Hervey, A. M. &c. 3 vols. London, 1755. [Presented by the Rev. Thomas Barton.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hildebrandus, 133, Q. B. D. Joach. Hildebrandi Historia Conciliorum a N. C. usq; ad Seculi XVII. annum XLV. in Ecclesia habitorum, Anno Christi MDCL. in illustri Academia Julia exposita, &c. &e. Helmstadii, 1715.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Histoire Ecclesiastique, 317, O. Histoire Ecclésiastique des Eglises Reformées au Royaume de France en laquelle est descrite au vray la renaissance et accroissement d&apos;icelles depuis l&apos;an MDXXI. iusques en l&apos;année MDLXIII.   leur discipline, Synodes, persecutions, &c. &c. &c. avec le discours des premiers troubles ou guerres civiles, desquelles la vraye cause est aussi declarée. 3 tom. A Geneve, 1580.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hogan, 50—2, O. Strictures on a congress written by W. V. Harold entitled “A Reply to a Catholic Layman.&quot; By William Hogan. Philadelphia, 1822.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hooker, 59, F. The Works of that learned and judicious Divine, Mr. Richard Hooker, in eight books of Ecclesiastical Polity; with several other Treatises by the same author, and an Account of his Life and Death. London, 1676.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hooker,  227, O. A isthful Abridgment of the Works of that iuarned and judicious Divine, Mr. Richard Hooker.– With his Life. London, 1705.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Huls, 296, O. Omnium Romanorum Pontificum Vitae, quas ipsis autorum pontificiorum verbis, multo labore et studio descripsit, Wilhelmus Huls, Eccl. Gall. Vesal. Minister. Vesaliae, 1639.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jonstonus, 32, D. Arturi Jonstoni Psalmi Davidici, cum Argumentis et Notis. Londini, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Junius, 222, O. Sacrorum Parallelorum libri tres: id est, Comparatio locorum Scripturae Sacrae, qui ex Testamento Vetere in Novo adducuntur, etc. &c. Francisci Junii, Biturigis. Parisiis, 1610.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Keller, 122—6, Q. De Philosophiæ cum Theologia Concordia et Usu, &c. Auct. J. H. Keller. Coburgi, 1698.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kettlewell, 115—3, F. The Practical Believer; or, the Articles of the Apostles&apos; Creed, drawn out to form a true Christian’s Heart and Practice. By John Kettlewell. London, 1703.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kettlewell, 213, O. An Help and Exhortation to Wothy Communicating, Lc. &c. With suitable Devotions added By John Kettlewell, B. D. &c. London, 1737.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>King, 84 O. An Essay on the Origin of Evil; by Dr. William King, late Archbishop of Dublin. Translated from the Latin with large Notes. Also, Two Sermons by the same Author, on Divine Prescience and the Fall of Man. By Edmund Law, D. D. &c. Cambridge, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kunze, 314, O. Einige Gedichte und Lieder von Johann Christoph Kunze, Ev. Luth. Pred. zu Philadelphia. Philadelphia, 1778. [Presented by the Author.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lactantius, 173, O. Lucii Coelii Lactantii Firmiani Opera quae extant. Cum selectis Variorum Commentariis, opera et studio Servatii Gallaei. Lugduni Batavorum, 1660.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lactantius,  344, O. L. Coelii Lactantii Firmiani Opera, quae extant, omnia. Accedunt Carmina vulgo asscripta Lactantio. Cum Notis Antonii Thysii, J. C. &c. Lugduni Batavorum, 1652.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lectures, 103, O. Theological Lectures read in the public Hall of the University of Edinburgh. With Exhortations to the Canditates, &c. Rules and Iustructions for a holy Life, &c.&c. London, 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ledermann, 121—1, Q. De adaequato sacrae Scripturae Criterio, &c. &c. Auctt- P. P. A. Ledermann et J. Müller.Bambergæ, 1783.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Leighton, 102, O. Select Works of Archbishop Leighton. With an Account of his Life and Character. London, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lightfoot, 38, F. The Works of the Rverend and Learned John metfoot, D. D. late Master of Katherine Hall in Cambridge.  With his Life. Portrait and Maps. 2 vols. London, 1684.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Limborch, 113, F. Philippi a Limborch SS. Theol. inter Remonstrantes Prof. Theologia Christiana ad praxin pietatis ac promotionem pacis Christianae unice directa. Item, Relatio Historica de Origine et Progressu Contoversi arum in Foederato Belgio de Praedestinatione. Amstelædami, 1715.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Limmer, 97—1, Q. Trauerrede auf den Hochw. Fürsten und Herrn Franz Ludwig, Bischof zu Bamberg, &c.&c. März 7, 1795, von G. I. Limmer.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Loscanus, 123—4, Q. scientiae philosophico-theologicae experimentum tertium, &c. &c Auct. J. F. Loscano. Helmstadii, 1716.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mariemon, 116, Q. Constitutiones de fundamentis legis Rabbi Mosis F. Maiiemon. Latinè redditae per Guil. Vorstium C. F. Additis quibusdam Notulis, et Abravanelis scripto, de Fidei Capite. Hebr. et Lat. Amstelodami, 1638.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Maimonides, 98, Q. Misnae Pars: ordinis primi Zeraim tituli septem. Latinè vertit et Commentario illustravit Gulielmus Guisius. Accedit Mosis Maimonidis Praefatio in Misnam, Edv. Pocockio Interprete. Oxoniae, 1690.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Masonus, 129, F. Vindiciae Ecclesiae Anglicanae; sive de legitimo ejusdem Ministerio, id est, de Episcoporum Successione, Electione, Consecratione, et Confirmatione; item, de Presbyterorum, et Diaconorum Ordinatione, Libri V. In quibus Ecclesia Anglicana à Bellarmini, Sanderi, &c. &c. &c. calumniis, &c, &e. vindicatur. Author e Franc. Masono, S. T. B. &c. Londini, 1638.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Molitor. 142—1, Q. De Sacramentis in genere, &e. &c. Auct. D. J. Molitor. Bambergæ, 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nadler, 110—8, Q. De Deo Uno et Trino, &c.&c. Auct. P. Ph. Nadler. Bambergæ, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nadler, 121—7, Q. De Deo Uno et Trino, &c. &c (Auct. P. P). Nadler. Bambergæ, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Niecampius, 101, Q. B. Jo Lucae Niecampii Historia Missionis Evangelicae in India Orientali e copiosis illius actis contracta: in Latinum Linguam translata et aucta a Jo. H. Grischovio. Cum Praefatione D. G. A. Franckii. Halae, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nieuwentyt, 159, O. The religious Philosother: or, the right use of Contemplating the Works of the Creator, Lc. &c.  Sesigned for the Conviction of Atheists and Infidels, &c. &c. By Dr. Nieuwentyt. Translated from the Low Bulch, by John Chamberlayne, Esq. F. R. S. With a Letter, by J. T. Desaguliers, F. R. S. &c. plates. 3 vols. London, 1730.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Novum Testamentum, 3, 0. Novum Testamentum Graece, ex recensione Jo. Jac. Griesbachii, cum selecta Lectionum Varietate. Tom. 2 in 1. Cantabrigiæ, Nov-Anglorum, 1809. [Presented by W. Hillard.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Novum Testamentum, 39, F. Novum Testamentum Græce. Cum Lectionibus variantibus MSS. Exemplarium, Versionum, Editionum, SS. Patrum et Scriptorum Ecclesiasticorum; et in easdem Notas. Accedunt Loca Scripturae Parallela, &c. &c. Præmittitur Dissertatio, &c. studio et Labore Joannis Millii, S. T. P. Oxonii, 1707.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ott, 142 —3, Q. Ad Doctrinam de Sacramenta Matrimoni Diatriba, &c. &c Auct. D. H. Ott. Bambergae, 1766.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pabstmann, 142—2, Q. Ad Doctrinam de Sacramento ordinis Diatriba, &c. &c Auct. D. M. Pabstmann. Bambergae, 1765.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Parecbolæ, 347, O. Parecholae sive, Excerpta è Corpore Statutorum Universitatis Oxoniensis. Accedunt Articuli Religionis XXXIX. in Ecclesia Anglicana recepti: nec non Juramenta Fidelitatis et Suprematus. Oxonii, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pearson, 107, F. An Exposition of the Creed. By John Pearson, D. D. &c. London, 1669.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pegorier, 137, Q. Systeme de la Religion Protestante. Par M. Còsar Pégorier. , 1717.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pennington, 82, Q. The Works of the long-mournful and sorely- distressed Isaac Penington, whom the Lord, in his tender mercy, at length visited and believed by the ministry of that despised People called Quakers, &c. c. &c., 2 vols. London, 1761. [Presented by the Quakers in London.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Picart, 9, F. The Ceremonies and Religious Customs of the various Nations of the known World: together with Historical Annotations, and several curious Discleuses equally instructive and entering. Written originally in French, and lllustrated with a large number of folio Copper Srates, all beautifully designed by Mr. Bernard Picart, and curiously engraved by most of the best hands in Europe. Faithfully translated into English, by a Gentleman late of St. John&apos;s College in 0xford. 6 vols. London, 1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Psalterium, 128, F. Quincuplex Psalterium; Gallicum, Romanum, Hebraicum, Vetus, Conciliatum. Parisiis, 1509.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Relandus, 633, O. Antiquitates Sacrae Veterum Hebraeorum breviter delineatae ab Hadriano Relando. Trajecti Batavorum, 1717.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Revelation, &c. 245, O. revelation examined with Candour, &c. Vol. II. London, 1735.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Roppelt, 121—3, Q. Theses dogmaticae, &c.&c. Auct. P. J. Roppelt. Bambergæ, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rosæus, 359, O. Virgilii Evangelisantis Christiados Libri XIII. In quibus omnia quae de Domino nostro J. Christo in utroque testamento, vel dicta vel praedicta sunt, altisona divini Maronis tuba suavissime decantantur. Inflante Alexandre Rosaeo, Aberdonense. Londini, 1638.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sacerdotium, 146—1, Q. Regale Sacerdotium detineatum, &c. &c &c. Wirceburgi, 1737.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schleicher, 110—9, Q. Historiae Ecclesiasticae Seculum Primum, &c. &c. Auct. G. J. Schleicher. Bambergæ, 1776.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schmittlein, 144—5, Q. De Sacramento Poeniteniæ, &c. &e.&c. Auct. D. N. Schmittlein. Bambergae, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schnapp, 121—6, Q. Ultimum Christi Pascha, &c. Auct. J. K. Schnapp. Bambergæ, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Scholar’s daual, 232, O. The Scholar&apos;s Manual: being a collection of Meditations, Reflections and Reasonings, designed for establishing and promoting Christian Principles and Pracite, in irreligious and sceptical Times. With suitable Devotions. By a Gentleman of Oxford. London, 1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schott, 91—3, Q. Concilia Synodi et Comitia Sacra Bambergensia, & c. &c. Auct. J. Schott. Bambergae, 1770.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>121—5, Q. Cohærentia doctrinae theologicae de fide, &c. &c. Auct. J. Schott. Bambergæ, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schott, 146—4, Q. Cohærentia Doctrinae Theologicæ de Fide et Statu Fidei, &c. & c. Ac. Auct. D. J. Schott. Bambergae, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schwelingius, 60, D. Mens immortalis evidenter certò contra Atheos Scepticosque, demonstrata a Johanne Eberhardo Schwelingio. Bremæ, 1683.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Seelman, 122—4, Q. Infallibilis summi Pontificis supra Concilium Oecumenicum in decidendis Fidei Controversiis Authoritas, &c. &c Auct. D. A. Seelman. Bambergae, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Semmelmann, 122—1, Q. Theses de Magno Pietatis Sacramento, quod manifestatum est in carne, I. Tim. III. 16, &c. &c. Auct. D. J. Semmelmann. Bambergæ, 1766.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sermons, 33, D. Sermons sur tous les Sujets de la Morale Chretienne. Par le R. P. * *, de la Compagnie de Jesus.— Tom. IV. A Paris, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sewel, 101, F. The history of the Rise, Increase and progress of the Christian People called Quakers: intermixed with several remarkable occurrences. Written originally in Law Dutch, and also translated into English, by William Sewel. London, 1725.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sherlock, 243, O. A Proctical Discourse concerning future Judgment. By William Sherlock, D. D. &c. London, 1725.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sherlock,  261, O. The Use and lntent of Prophecy, in the several ages of the World, &c. Also, four Dissertations, I. The Authority of the 2d Epistle of St. Peter. II. The sense of the Antients, &c. on the Fall. III. The Blessing of Judah, Gen. xlix. IV. Christ’s Entry into Jerusalem. By Thomas Sherlock, D. D. &c. London, 1735.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sherlock,  262, O. A Discourse concerning the Divine Providence. By William Sherlock, D. D. London, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Spanhemius, 339, O. Pro Friderico Spanhemio adversus Fictiones Nuperi Criminatoris de varia et libera Ecclesiarum Politia, deque Anglicano Episcopatu, Animadversionum Pars Specialis. Lugduni Batavorum, 1684.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stelzig, 110—7, Q. De Deo Uno et Trino, &c. &c¬&c. Auct. D. Carolo Stelzig. Bambergæ, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stenglein, 110—6, Q. Character Jansenisticæ Factionis, &c. &c Auct. P. J. Stenglein. Bambergae, 1770.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Swedenborg, 48, O. True Christian Religion; containing the Universal Theology of the New Church, &c. &c &c., By E Geauek Swedenborg. Translated from the Original Latin. 2 vols. Philadelphia, 1789.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theophyl1actus, 82, F. Theophylacti, Archiepiscopi Belgariæ Commentarii in Quatuor Evangelia. Graecè et Latinè. Cum Notulis, variis Lectionibus, &c. Tom. 2. Lutetiae Parisiorum, 1635.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theologia, 142—6, Q. Theses selectae ex universa Theologia revelata, &c.&c. Bambergæ, 1779.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Turretinus, 114, Q. Institutio Theologicae Eleneticae, in qua Status Contromversiae exponitur, &c. &e. Authori Francisco Turretino, SS. T. Pr. Pars secunda. Lugduni  Batavorum, 1696.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Twissus 113, Q. Vindiciae Gratiæ, Potestatis, ac Providentiae Dei: hoc est, ad Examen libelli Perkinsiani, de Praedestinationis modo et ordine, institutum à Jacobo Arminio, Responsio Scholastica. Una cum Digressionibus, &c. &c. &c. Auctore Guilielmo Twisso, SS. T. D. Amsterdami, 1632.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vetus Testamentum, 36, Q. Vetus Testamentum ex versione septuaginta Interpretum, secundum Exemplar Vaticanum Romae editum, una cum Scholiis ejusdem Editionis, Variis MStorum Codicum Veterumque Exemplarium Lectionibus, nec non Fragmentis Versionum Aquilae, Symmachi et Theodotionis. Summa cura edidit Lambertus Bos, L. Gr. Prof. Tom. 2. Franequeræ, 1709.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vries, 1853, O. Gerardi de Vries, Phil. Prof. de Natura Dei et Humanae Mentis Determinationes pneumatologicae. Accedunt de Catholicis rerum Attributis ejusdem Determinationes Ontologicae. Ultrajecti, 1690.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Werner, 144—3, Q. Die Sechste Lob-Predig, &c. &c.. Von J. Werner, &c. Bambergæ, 1715.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wagner, 110—10, Q. Oratio Jesu Montanae pars insignior apud Matth. Cap. V. Notis philologico exegeticis illustrata Auct. J.J. Wagner. Bambergæ, 1798.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Weyermann, 110—1, Q. Trauerrede auf den Herrn Gallus, Abt und Prälat, &c. Von G. Fr. Weyermann. Bamberg, 7ten May, 1799.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Weyermann, 110—2, Q. De Apostolorum olim Divo Petro Superstitum ad Episcopum Romanum Divi Petri Successorem ordine in Praefectura Ecclesiæ, &c. Auct. D. G. F. Weyer mann. Bambergæ, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Weyermann, 121—4, Q. Trauerrede auf den Herrn Karl Theodorick, von und zu Guttenberg, &c. von G. F. Weyermann, den 14ten April. Bamberg, 1794.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Weyermann,  121—9, Q. Trauerrede auf Joseph den Zweiten den allerdurchlauchtigsten Römischen Kayser, von G. F. Weyermann, den 20ten April, 1790. Bamberg, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Whiston 202, O. Six Dissertations; on Josephus; Reply to Dr. Sykes, on the Chronology of the Scriptures, &c. &c., By William Whiston, M. A. London, 1734.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wideburgius, 117, Q. Mat fois Biblica septem speciminibus comprehensa, exhibens explicationes locorum mathematicorum quae per Universam Scripturam V. et N. Testamenti occurrunt. Autore Jo. Bernhardo Wideburgio, Math. Prof. Jenensi, &c. Jenae, 1730.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wilson, 49, F. The Works of the Rt. Rev. Father in God, Thos. Wilson, D. D. fifty-eight years Lord Bishop of Sodor and Man. With his Life, by the Rev. C. Crutwell. 2 vols. in 1. London, 1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Winckellmann, 123—3, Q. Lob-und Trauer-Rede auf den Herrn Gallus, & c. &c. Von A. R. P. G. Windkellmann, den 12ten Februar. Augspurg, 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aelianus, 322, O. Cl. AEliani Sophistae variae Historiae, cum Notis Joannis Schefferi. Graece et Latine. Argentorati, 1647.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aesopus, 360, O. Selectiores Æsopi Phrygis Fabulae, et Luciani Samosatensis Dialogi. Isocratis Orationes duae, ad Demonicum et Nicoclem. Cebetis Thebani Tabula: nec non Galeni Pergameni Suasoria ad artes Oratio. Graece et Latine. Edinburgi, 1767.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Anacreon, 38, D. Anacreen Teius, Poeta Lyricus, summa cura, ad fidem etiam Vet. me. Vatican. emendatus. Aliquot justis Poematiis, et Fragmentis plurimis, auctus. Item, Anacreontis Sea, &c. &e. Opéra et Studio Josuae Barnes, S. T. B. Græce et Latine. Cum Effigiis. Cantabrigiæ, 1705.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Antoninus, 94, Q. Marci Antonini Imperatoris de rebus suis; sive de eis quae ad se pertinere censebat, Libri XII. Locis haud paucis repurgati, suppleti, restituti: Versione Latina nova; Lectionibus variis, Locis parallelis; ac Commentario perpetuo explicati et illustrati. studio Operâque Thomae Gatakeri. Accessere Annotationes selectiores A. D’Acerii, necnon Marci Antonini Vita, &c. &c. a Geo. Stanhope. Græce et Latine. Londini, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Apuleius, 318, O. L. Apuleii Madaurensis Opera omnia quae exstant, emendata et aucta; cura Petri Colvii Brugensis; cum ejusdem ad omnia uberioribus Notis. Accessit, inter alia, Liber de Syllogismo Categorico, &c. Lugduni Batavorum, 1688.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristophanes, 53, D. Aristophanis Comoediae undecim, Graece et Latine, cum Fragmentis et emendationibus virorum doctorum, praecipue Josephi Scaligeri. Lugduni Batavorum, 1625.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristoteles, 43, F. Aristotelis Stagiritæ Opera omnia quae exstant. Græcè et Latinè, cum Notis, Emendationibus, &c. Is. Casauboni aliorumque virorum doctorum. Acesserunt Kyriaci Strozæ libri duo Politicorum Graecolatini; item, Pragmenta ex libris Aristotelis qui hodie non supersunt, &c. &c. Tom. 2. Aureliæ Allobrogum, 1605.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristoteles, 276, O. Aristotelis Stagiritæ Opera, Graece et Latine.— Tom. I. Aureliæ Allobrogum, 1607.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristoteles, 70, O. Aristotelis de Poetica liber, ex Versione Theodori Goulstoni. Lectionis Varietatem e Codd. IV. Bibl. Mediceae, Indicem et Observationes suas adjunxit T. Winstanley, A. M. & c. &c. Graece et Latine. Oxonii, 1780.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristoteles, 128, Q. Aristotelis Physicae auscultationis libri 8.—De Coelo, 4.—De seneratione et Corruptione, 2.—Meteorologicorum, 4.—De Mundo, 1.—De Anima, 3.—De Sensu et Sensilibus, 1.—De Memoria et Reminiscentia, 1.—De Somno et Vigilia, 1.—De Insomniis, 1.-De Divinatione per Somnum, 1.—De Juventute, Senectute, Vita et Worte, 1.-De Respiratione, I.-De Longitudine et Brevitate Vitae, 1.— Addita in tractatus cujusque fine varia locorum lectio; Inventaria rerum et verborum, &c. & c. Græcè et Latinè. Francofurti, 1596.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aurelius Victor, 156, O. Sexti Aurelii Victoris Historiae Romanae Breviarium, illustratum And. Schotti, Dom. Machanei, Jani Gruteri, et Annae Tanaquili Fabri Filiae Commen tariis: ut et Cæsarum, Augustorum, etc. &c. iconibus ex nummis veteribus expressis, in æs incisis. Curâ et labore Samuelis Pitisci. Trajecti ad Rhenum, 1696.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ausonius, 79, D. Magni Ausonii Burdig. viri consularis, Opera, a Josepho Scaligero, et Elia Vineto, recognita, disposita, et variorum Notis illustrata, &c.&c. &c. Mannhemii, 1795</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boethius, 259, O. An. Manl. sever. Boethii Consulationis Philosophiae, libri V. Ejusd. Opuscula Sacra. Cum integris Notis Johannis Bernartii, Theodori Sitzmani, et Renati Vallini. Accedit Petri Bertii Praefatio.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catullus, 71, D. Catullus, Tibulus, Propertius, cum C. Galli Fragmentis, serio castigati. Amstelædami, 1686.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catullus, 310, O. Catulli, Tiballi, Propertii, nova editio. Josephus Scaliger, Jul. Cæsaris F. recensuit. Ejusdem in eosdem Castigationum Liber. Lutetiae, 1577.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cicero, 38, Q. Marci Tullii Ciceronis Opera, quae supersunt, omnia, cum Asconio et Scholiaste veteri; ac Notis Integris P. Victorii, J. Camerarii, F. Ursini, et selectis P. Manutii, D. Lambini, J. Gulielmii, Jn. Gruteri, 3. F. et J. Gronoviorum, J. G. Graevii et aliorum quamplurimorum, qui aliquam Ciceronis Operum Partem, Animadversionibus illustraverunt. Isaacus Verburgius collegit, disposuit, recensuit, &c. &c.c. &c. Tom. 4. Amstelædami, 1724.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cicero,  65, D. M. Tulli Ciceronis Opera omnia, post Dion. Lambini, Mich. Bruti, Dion. Gothofredi, Al. Scot, aliorum que editiones. Cum Alexandri Scot. sectionibus Apparatui Latinae locutionis respondentibus. 8 tom. in 7. Lngduni, 1609.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cicero, 29, D. M. Tullii Ciceronis de Officiis, libri tres. Item, Cato Major, Lælius, Paradoxa, et Somnium Scipionis. Philadelphiæ, 1793.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Claudianus, 74, D. Cl. Claudiani quae exstant: ex emendatione Nicolai Heinsii, Dan. F. Amstelodami, apud Elzevirium, 1677.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cornelius Nepos, 73—1, D. Cornelii Nepotis excellentium Imperatorum Vitæ. Cui accessit Index Boecleri locupletissimus. Londini, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cornelius Nepos, 73—2, D. Corn. Nepos, vulgò AEmilius Probus, de Vita excellentium Imperatorum, selectissimis Notis variorum illustratus. Rotomagi, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Curtius, 311, O. Q. Curtius Rufus de Rebus Alexandri Magni. Nebst Teutschen Summarien, Teuschen Supplementis, &c. &c. &c. durch Emanuel Sincerum. Augspurg, 1716.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Demosthenes, 24, F. Demosthenis et Æschinis Principum Graeciae Oratorum Opera, cum utriusque autoris Vita et Ulpiani Commentariis, novisque Scholiis, ex Quarta eaque postrema recognitione, Graecolatina: variis Lectionibus adaueta, Annotationibus illustrata: per Hieron. Wol- fium. His recens accedit vita Demosthenis ex Parallelis Andreae Schotti. Tom. 3. Francofurti, 1604.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Diodorus, 70, D. Diodori Siculi Bibliothecae Historicae libri XVII. Lugduni, 1559.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dionysius, 290, O. Dionysii Geographia emendata et locupletata, Additione Seil. Geographiæ Hodiernae, Graeco Carmine. pariter donatae: cum 16 tabulis geographicis. Ab. Edw. Wells, A. M. &c. Græce et Latine. Oxonii, 1704.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Epictetus, 289, O. Epicteti Stoici Philosophi Enchiridion: una cum Cebetis Thebani Tabula. Quibus adjiciuntur Simplicii Commentarius in Enchiridion Epicteti. Item, Arriani Commentariorum de Epicteti Disputationibus, libri IV. Omnia Hieronymo Wolfio Interprete. Graece et Latine. Londini, 1670.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Euripides, 268, O. Euripidis Tragoediae octodecim, Graecè. Basileae, 1537.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Euripides, 183, O. Euripidis Hecuba, Orestes, et Phœnissæ, cum Scholiis antiquis; ac Versione, Notisque Johannis King, fere integris; curante Thoma Morell: qui Alcestin adjecit, cum Scholiis quae extent, nova Verdione, et Notis perpetuis. Graece et Latine. Tom. 2. Londini, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Euripides, 358, O. Euripidis Tragoediae duae, Medea et Alcestis; cum Interpretatione Latina Georgii Buchanani Scoti.— Græce et Latine. Edinburgi, 1722.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Florus, 44, D. L. Julii Flori Rerum a Romanis gestarum libri IV. A Johanne Stadio emendati. Seorsum excusus in eos Commentarius J. Stadii elaboratissimus. Cui accesserunt Chronologicae Cl. Salmasii exceptiones: una cum variis Lectionibus, &c.—Item, L. Ampelii Liber Memorialis, &c. Oxoniae, 1669.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Florus, 251, O. L. Annaei Flori Epitome Rerum Romanarum cum Notis integris Cl. Salmasii, et selectis Variorum. Accedunt Jo. Georgii Graevii Annotationes; nec non Numismata et antiqua Monumenta, cum Variantibus Lectionibus, &c. &c. &c. In fine additus est L. Ampelius. Amstelædami, 1682.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Florus, 212, O. L. Annæi Flori Epitome Rerum Romanarum. — With an English Translation as literal as possible. By John Clarke. Latin and English. London.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gellius, 325, O. A. Gellii luculentissimi Scriptoris, Noctes Atticae. Lugduni, 1571.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heliodorus, 312, O. Heliodori Aethiopicorum libri X. Ad fidem MSS. ab Hieronymo Commelino emendati, multis in locis aucti, ejusdemque Notis illustrati. Græce et Latine. Lugduni, 1611.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hesiodus, 131, O. Hésiodi Ascraei quæcumque exstant, Graece et Latine, ex recensione Joannis Clerici, cum ejusdem Animadversionibus. Cum Notis, &c. &ca Scaligeri, Heinsii, Guieti, S. Clerici, Grævii, et Pasoris. Amstelodami, 1701.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Historiae Augustæ Scriptores, 252, O. Historiæ Augustae Scriptores VI. Aelius Sportianus, Julius Capitolinus, AElius Lampridius, Vulc. Gallicanus, Trebell. Pollio, Flavius Vopiscus. Cum integris Notis Is. Casauboni, Cl. Salmasii, et Jani Gruteri, &c. Tom. 2. Lugduni Bata- vorum, 1671.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Historiae, 3, D. Secretae e profanis Scriptoribus Historiae. Philadelphiae, 1819.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Homerus, 72. Q. Homeri Opera Omnia, et in eadem Scholia, sive Interpretatio Veterum. Una cum Notis perpetuis, in Textum et Scholia, necnon Variis Lectionibus longè Plurimis, et Versione Latina, accuratiori limâ perpolita. Operâ, Studio, et Impensis, Josuae Barnes, S. T. B. &c. Tom. 2. Cantabrigiae, 1711.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Homerus, 114, O. Homeri Ilias, Græcè et Latinè. Cum Annotationibus Samuelis Clarke, S. T. P. Tom. 2. Londini, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Homerus, 115, O. Homeri Odyssea, Græcè et Latinè. Edidit, Annotationesque ex Notis nonnullis MStis. a Samuele Clarke, S. T. P. defuncto relictis, partim collectas, adjecit Samuel Clarke, Societ. Reg. Soc. Tom. 2. Londini, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Homerus, 69, O. Homeri Ilias, Græce et Latine. Cum Annotationibus Samuelis Clarke, S. T. P. Vol. II. Dublinii, 1787.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Isocrates, 100, F. Isocratis Scripta, quae quidem nunc extent, omnia, Graecolatina, postremo recognita: Annotationibus novis et eruditis illustrata, Castigationibusque necessariisque expolita: Hieronymo Wolfio ÇEtingensi interprete et auctore, &c. &c. Basilae, 1570.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jamblichus, 106, F. Jamblichi Chalcidensis ex Coele-Syria, de Mysteriis Liber. Præmittitur Epistola Porphyrii ad Anebonem Ægyptium, eodem argumento. Thomas Gale, Anglus Graece nunc primum edidit, Latine vertit, et Notas adjecit. Oxonii, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Juvenalis, 80, D. Junii Juvenalis et Auli Persii Flacci Satyræ, ex doctorum virorum emendatione. Hagæ-Comitum, 1683.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Justinus, 34, D. Justini ex Trogi Pompeii Historiis externis libri XLIV. Londini, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Justinianus, 346, O. Justiniani Augusti Historia, in qua Bellum Persicum, Vandilicum, Gothicum, Belisarii praesertim Narsetisque, prudentia &c. feliciter absolutum; opera autem et studio Procopii Cæsariensis, Agathiae Myrrinæi, Jornandis Alani, Libris XIII continetur. Accedunt Procopii de Justiniani Aedificiis Lib. VI. et Jornandis de regnorum et temporum Liber. etc. &c. Genevae, 1594.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Libanius, 98, F. Libanii Sophistae Opera Omnia; nunc primum prodeunt, parthm e Bibliotheca Regia, partim e Vaticana, aliisque. Fed. Morellus Prof. Reg. Decanus recensuit, castigavit, Latine vertit, et Notis illustravit. Graece et Latine. Tom. 2. Parisiis, 1606-1627.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lavius, 32, F. Titi Livii Patavini Historicorum Romanorum Principis, libri omnes superstites, recogniti et emendati ad MSS. Codd. Fuld. Mogunt. et Colon. fidem, à Francisco Modio; nunc etiam comparati cum Membranis Bibl. Palat. Elect., melioresque facti curâ tertiâ Jani Gruteri: cujus accedunt Notae criticae et politicae; nec non quinquaginta aliquot in Corn. Tacitum Discursus, &c. Francofurti ad Mœnum, 1628.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lavius, 343, O. Titi Livii Historiarum quod exstat, cum integris</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Joannis Freinshemii Supplementis, Tabulis Geographicis, &c. Recensuit et Notulis auxit Joannes Clericus. Tom. 10. Amstelædami, 1710.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Livius, 197, O. T. Livii Patavini Historiarum ab Urbe condita Libri. Tom. 2.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Longinus, 137, O. Dionysii Longini de Sublimitate Commentarius. Cum Versione et Notis Zachariae Pearce, A. M. &c. Accessit Fr. Porti Cretensis in Longinum Commentarius integer. Græce et Latine. Amstelædami, 1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucanus, 43, D. M. Annaeus Lucanus de Bello Civili: cum Hugonis Grotii, Fernabii Notis integris, et Variorum selectissimis; accurante Cornelio Schrevelio.—Item, Petronii Arbitri specimen Belli Civilis,—Item, Supplementum Lucani Libri septem. Author Thoma Maio, Anglo, &c. &c. Lugduni, 1670.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucanus, 127, F. M. Annei Lucani Pharsalia, cum duobus commentis Joannis Sulpitii Verulani et Omniboni Vicentini, &c. &c. Venetiis, 1505</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucianus, 280, O. Luciani Samosatensis Opera. Ex Versione Joannis Benedicti. Cum Notis integris Bourdelotii, Palmerii Tan. Fabri, Menagii, Guieti, Graevii, Gronovii, Barlaei, Tollii, et selectis aliorum. Accedunt inedita Scholia in Lucianum, ex Bibliotheca Isaaci Vossii. Græce et Latine. Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1687.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucianus, 45, D. Luciani Samosatensis Dalogorumölktorum libri duo, a Gulielmo Du-gardo recogniti, &c. Graece et Latine. Londini, 1737.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucian, 24, D. The select Dialogues of Lucian, in Greek. With a new literal Translation in Latin, and Notes in English. By Edward Murphy, M. A. Dublin, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucretius, 88, Q. T. Lucretii Cari de Rerum Natura, libri VI. a Dion. Lambino, Monstroliensi ex auctoritate quinque Codd. MSS. emendati, et commentariis illustrati, &c. &c. &c. Cum Via Lucretii, eodem Lambino auctore. Lutetiae, 1570.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lucretius, 286, O. M. Valerii Materialis Epigrammata, cum Notis Farnabii et Variorum. Accurante Cornelio Schrevelio. Lugduni Batavorum, 1661.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Minucius Felix, 132, O. M. Minucii Felicis Octavius cum integris omnium Notis, &c. novaque Recensione Jacobi Ouzelii. Cujus et accedunt Animadversiones. Insuper Joh. Meursii Notae. Et Liber Julii Firmici Materni, V. C. De Errore Profanarum Religionum. Lugduni Batavorum, 1672.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Minucius Felix, 329, O. Marci Minucii Felicis Octavius. Ex recensione Johannis Davisii. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Novus Historiarum Delectus, 255, O. Novus Historiarum Fabellarumque Delectus: cum Notis et Versione. Græce et Latine. In Usum Scholæ Etonensis. Londini, 1701.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Opuscula Mythologica, Ethica, et Physica, 297, O. Opusula Mythologica, Ethica, et Physica. Græce et Latine. Palaephatus, Heraclitus, Anonymus, Phurnutus, Sallustius, Ocellus Lucanus, Timaeus Locrus.—Demophilus, Democrates, Secundus, Sextius Pythagoricus, Theophrasti Characteres, Pythagoricorum Fragmenta.—Heliodori Larissæi Optica. Cantabrigiæ, 1671.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ovidius, 196, O. P. Ovidii Nasonis Opera Omnia, cum integris Nicolai Heinsii, D. F. lectissimisque Variorum Notis: quibus non pauca, ad suos quaeque antiquitatis fontes diligenti comparatione reducta, accesserunt, studio Borchardi Cnippingii. Tom. 3. Amstelodami, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ovidius 266. O. P. Ovidii Nasonis Opera Omnia, cum integris Nic Heinsii, D. F. lectissimisque Variorum Notis, &c. &c. Studio Borchardi Cnippingii. Tom. 3. Lugduni Batavorum, 1670.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pausanias, 112, F. Pausaniae accurata Græciæ Descriptio, à Guilielmo Xylandro Augustano diligenter recognita, accesserunt Annotationes G. Xylandri et Frid. Sylburgi, et Romuli Amasaei Versio, &c. &cGraece et Latine.—  Hanoviae, 1613.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Phædrus 77, O. Phædri Augusti Cæsaris Liberti, Fabularum Aesopiarum libri quinque; una cum Clave, &c. et Notis  Petri Daneti, &c. &c.. &c. Latine et Anglice. Opera et Studio N.edley. Londini, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Phædrus 6, D. The Fables of Phædrus in Latin, with English Notes and a Vocabulary. Baltimore, 1827. (Presented by the Rev. Charles Williams.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Phalaris, 201, O. Phalaridis Agrigentinorum Tyranni Epistolae. Ex. MSS. recensuit, Versione. Annotationibus, et Vita insuper Authoris donavit Car. Boyle ex Æde Christi Graece et Latine. Oxonii.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pindarus, 15, D. Omnia Pindari quae extent. Olympia, Pythia, Nemea, Isthmia. Cum Interpretatione Latina. Graece et Latine. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pindarus, 110, F. Pindari blympia, Nemea, Isthmia. Una cum Latina omnium Versione Carmine Lyrico per Nicolaum Sudorium, Scholiis antiquis Graecis, Variantibus Lectionibus, Vita Pindari, Chronologia Olympionicarum, &c. &c. &c. Oxonii, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plato, 269, O. Platonis Philosophi quae exstant Graece ad editionem Henrici Stephani accurate expressa, cum Marsilii Ficini Interpretatione, Praemittitur L. III. Laertii de Vita et Dogm. Platonis. Cum Notitia Literaria. Accedit Varietas Lectionis. Tom. 12. Biponti, 1781.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plato, 200, O. Platonis Phaedo. Scholarum in usum seorsum, cum Annotatione perpetua edidit, L. H. Heindorfius. Graece. Berolini, 1810.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plato,  22, D Platonis Apologia Socratis.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plato,  22, D Platonis Apologia Socratis. Crito.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plato,  22, D Platonis Apologia Socratis. Alcibiades Secundus.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plato,  22, D Platonis Apologia Socratis. Cebetis Thebani Tabula.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophontis Prodici Mercules. Græce et Latine. Abredoniae, 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plautus, 265, O. M. Accii Plauti Comœdiæ. Accedit Commentarius ex Variorum Notis et Observationibus, &c. &c. Ex recensione Joh. Frederici Gronovii. Lugduni Batavorum, 1664.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plautus, 275, O. M. Accii Plauti Comœdiae, cum Commentariis Variorum ex recensione Joh. Frederici Gronovii. Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1684.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plautus, 292, O. M. Accii Plauti, Sarsinatis Umbi Comœdiae XX. superstites et deperditarum fragmenta. Philippus Pareus tertium recensuit: ac Notis perpetuis illustravit. Francofurti, 1641.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plinius, 41, D. C. Plinii Caecilii Secundi Epistolae et Panegyricus Trajano dictus. Recensuit Joannes Nic. Lallemand. Parisiis, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plinius, 87, F. C. Plinii Secundi Historiae Mundi libri triginta septem. Cura Des. Erasmi Roterodami. Cum Castigationibus Sigismundi Gelenii. Lugduni, 1548.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plotinus, 125, F. Plotini Divini illius è Platonica familia Philosophi, De rebus Philosophicis libri LIII. in Enneades sex distributi, à Marsilio Ficino Florentino è Graeca lingua in Latinam versi, et ab eodem doctissimis commentariis. illustrati, omnibus cum Graeco exemplari collatis et diligenter castigatis. Basileae, 1559.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plutarchus, 117. F. Plutarchi Chaeronei, Philosophi, Historicique, Clarissimi, Opuscula (quae quidem extant) omnia, undequaque collecta, et diligentissimé jampridem recognita. Latine. Basileae, 1530.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Plutarchus,  57, F. Plutarchi Chaeronensis Moralia, Gulielmo Xylandro interprete. Graece et Latine. Francofurti, 1620.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Poetæ Minores Græci, 320, O. Poetae Minores Graeci, Hesiodus, Theocritus, Moschus, Bion, Smyra. Simmias, Rhod. Musæus, Theognis, Phocylides, Pythagoras, Solon, Tyrtaeus, Simonides, Rhianus, Naumachius, Panyasis, Orpheus, Mimnermus, Linus, Callimachus, Evenus. Par. Eratosthenes, Menecrates, Posidippus, Metrodorus.— Fragmenta quaedam Philemonis, Alexidis, Amphidis, Anaxandridae, Antiphanis. Apollodori, Diphili, Menandri, Diodori, Sinop. Eubuli, Hipparchi, Nicostrati, Pherecratis, Philippi, Sotadae, Cratetis, Eriphi, Posidippi, Timoclis, Clearchi, et aliorum incertorum Autorum. Accedunt Observationes Radulphi Wintertoni in Hesiodum. Græce et Latine. Cantabrigiae, 1677.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Poetæ Minores Græci, 304, O. Poeta Minores Graeci, selecti et emendati: scilicet, Hesiodus, Theocritus, Moschus, Bion, Smyrn. Musæus, Theognis, Phocylides, Pythagoras. Cum explicatione grammatica vocum difficiliorum, et tabulis aere incisis. Græce et Latine. Londini, 1739.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Poetæ Latini Minores, 335, O. Poetae Latini Minores, Faliscus, M. Aur. Ol. Nemesianus, T. Cal. Siculus, Cl. Rutilius, Q. Ser. Samonicus, Marcellus Q. Rh. Fannius, Sulpicia, ex editione Petri Burmanni fideliter expressi. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pomponius Mela, 337, O. Pomponii Melae libri tres de Situ Orbis, nummis antiquis et notis illustrati a Jacobo Gronovio. Julii Honorii Oratoris Excerpta Cosmographiae ab eodem nunc primum ex Ms. edita. Cosmographia, falso Aethicum auctorem praeferens, cum variis Lectionibus e Ms. Ravennas Geographus, ex Ms. Lugdunensi suppletus. Lugduni Batavorum, 1696.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pomponius Mela, 158, O. Pomponii Melae de Situ Orbis, libri III. Cum Notis Integris H. Barbari, P. G. Olivarii, F. N. Pintiani, P. Ciacconii, A. Schotti, J. Vossii, et J. Gronovii. Accedunt Julii Honorii Oratoris Exscripta Cosmographiae, &c. &c. &c. Curante Ab. Gronovio. Tom. 2. Lugduni Batavorum, 1722.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Porphyrius, 105. Q. Porphyrii Phoenicis Isagoge, id est, Introductio in Dialecticen. Item, Aristotelis Stagiritæ</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Principis Philosophorum Opera omnia, quae pertinent ad lnventionem et judicationem Dialecticæ. Partim Argyropolo Bizantino, partim Boethio Severino interprete. Coloniæ, 1586.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Quintilianus, 284, O. M. Fabii Quintiliani Institutionum Oratoriarum libri duodecim.—Declamationes undaviginti. M. Fabii Avi et Calpurnii Flacci Declamationes. Auctoris incerti Dialogus, de causis corruptae Eloquentiae. Cum Variorum Notis. Tom. 2. Lugduni Batavorum, 1665.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Quintus Curtius, 81, D. Quintus Curtius Rufus de Rebus gestis Alexandri Magni Regis Macedonum, cum supplementis, &c.&c.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Quintus Curtius, 216, O. quintus Curtius de Rebus gestis Alexandri Magni Regis Macedonum. Cum Notis et J. Freinshemii Supplementis, &c. &c, Londini.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Scriptores Rei Rusticæ, 71, Q. Scriptores Rei Rusticæ veteres Latini, Cato, Varro, Columella, Palladius, quibus nunc accedit Vegetius de Mulo-Medicina, et Gargilii Martialis Fragmentum, cum editionibus prope omnibus et MSS. pluribus collati, objectae Notae Virorum Clariss. integrae tum editae tum ineditae, et Lexicon Rei Rusticae, curante Jo. Matthia Gesnero: cum figuris. Lipsiae, 1735.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Seneca, 80, F. L. Annæus Seneca, a M. Antonio Mureto correctus et Notis illustratus. Accedunt seorsim, Animadversiones Jani Gruteri. 1594.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Seneca, 50, D. L. Annæi Senecæ Tragoediæ, cum Notis Farnabii. Amstelodami, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Silius Italicus, 161, O. Caii Silii Italici Punicorum libri septemdecim, Varietate Lectionis et perpetua adnotatione illus- trati a G. Alex. Ruperti. Cum Præfatione Chr. Gottl. Heyne. Tom. 2. Goettingæ, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sophocles, 89, O. Sophoclis Tragœdiæ Septem: nova versione donatae, Scholiisque veteribus illustratae; accedunt Notae perpetuae, et Variæ Lectiones, Opera Thomae Johnson, A. M., &c. Accessere etiam Notae selectae et Emendationes ex Codd. Variorum doctorum Virorum, nuper editis. Graece et Latine. Tom. 2. Etonae, 1775.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sophocles,  298, O. Sophoclis Tragoediae VII. Una cum omnibus graecis Scholiis ad calcem adnexis. Graece et Latine. Cantabrigiæ, 1669.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sophocles, 27, D. Sophoclis Tragoediæ, cum Versione Latina et selectis quibusdam Lectionibus. Græce et Latine.—Tom. 2. Londini, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tacitus, 116, D. C. Cornelii Taciti Opera, quae exstant, integris J. Lipsii, Rhenani, Ursini, Mureti, Pichenae, Merceri, Gruteri, Acidalii, Grotii, Freinshemii, et selectis aliorum commentariis illustrata. Joh. Fred. Gronovius recensuit, et suas Notas passim adjecit. Accedunt Jac. Gronovii excerpta ex variis Lectt. Ms. Oxon.- Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1685.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tacitus, 59, D. C. Cornelii Taciti Opera quae supersunt, Ex editione Jacobi Gronovii fideliter expressa. Tom. 4. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tacitus, 76, D. C. Cornelius Tacitus, cum optimis exemplaribus collatus. Amstelodami, apud Elzevirium, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Terentius, 77, D. Pub. Terentii Comœdiæ sex, ex recensione Heinsiana. Amstelodami.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Themistius, 16, F. Themistii Orationes XXXIII. e quibus tredecim nunc primum in lucem editae. Dionysius Petavius e Soc. Jesu latine plerasque reddidit, ac fere vicenas Notis illustravit. Accesserunt ad easdem XX. Orationes Notae alternae ad reliquas tredecim perpetuae Observationes Joannis Harduini. Graece et Latine.- Parisiis, 1684.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theophrastus, 209, O. Theophrasti Characteres Eshici. Græce et Latine. Cum Notis ac Emendationibus Isaaci Casauboni et aliorum. Accedunt Jacobi Duporti Praelectiones. Graeca cum vetustissimis MSS. collata, recensuit et Notas adjecit Pet. Reedham, S. T. B. &c. Cantabrigiæ, 1712.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theophrastus, 319, O. Theophrasti Narrationes Morum. Isaacus Casaubonus recensuit, in Latinum sermonem vertit, et Libro Commentario illustravit. Graece et Latine.— Lugduni, 1638.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tibullus, 334, O. Tibulli et Propertii Opera. Ex editione J.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Broukhusii fideliter expressa. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Velleius Paterculus, 340, O. Cail Velleii Paterculi quae supersunt ex Historiae Romanae voluminibus duobus. Ex editione Petri Burmanni fideliter expressa. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Velleius Paterculus, 351, O. P. Velleii Paterculi Hist. Rom. ad M. Vinicum Cos. libri duo. Cum Annotatis Jo. Henrici Boecleri.- Argentorati, 1663.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Virgilius, 51, Q. P. Virgilii Maronis Opera, cum integris Commentariis Servii, Philargyrii, Pierii. Accedunt Scaligeri et Lindenbrogii Notae ad Culicem, Cirin, Catalecta. Ad Cod. MS. Regium Parisiensem recensuit Pancratius Masvicius. Cum figuris, &c. Tom. 2. Leovardiae, 1717.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Virgilius,108, O. P. Virgilii Maronis Opera. Interpretatione et Notis illustravit Carolus Ruaeus, Soc. Jesu, ad usum Delphini. Londini, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Virgilius, 11, Q. Publii Virgilii Maronis Bucolica, Georgica, et Aeneis. Birminghamiae, apud Baskerville, 1757. (Presented by J. Penn.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Virgilius,66. D. Publii Virgilii Maronis Bucolica, Georgica, et Aneis. Cantabrigiæ, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophon, 67, F. Xenophontis, Philosophi et Imperatoris clarissimi, quae exstant Opera, cum Nova Adpendice, &c. Opera Joannis Leunclavii Amelburni. Accesserunt Aemilii Porti, Fr. Porti Cr. Fil. Notæ, &c. &c, & c. Græcè et Latinè. Lutetiae Parisiorum, 1625.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophon, 177. O. Xenophontis de Cyri Institutione libri Octo. Cum Notis Stephani, Leunclavii, Porti et Mureti, Variis Lectionibus, &c &c. &e. Cura Thomæ Hutchinson, A. M. Græce et Latine. Londini, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophon, 83, O. Xenophontis de Cyri Expeditione libri septem, a Thoma Hutchinson. Graece et Latine. Cantabrigiæ, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophon, 260, O. Xerophontis Memorabilium Socratis Dictorum, libri IV. Graece et Latine. Cum Notis Integris Ernesti, aliorumque Selectis, &c. &c. Oxonii, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophon, 338, O. Xenophontis de Agesilao Rege Oratio. Adjecta est Versio Latina ex editione T. Hutchinson. Graece et Latine. Glasguae, apud Foulis, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Academia Oxoniensis, 70, F. Academiae Oxoniensis Comitia Philologica in Theatro Sheldoniano decimo die Julii, A. D. 1713. Celebrata in Honorem Ser. Reginæ Annae Pacificae. Oxonii, 1713.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Administulum Puerile, 23, D. Adminiculum Puerile: or, an Help for Schoolboye, &c. &c- Philadelphia, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ainsworth, 90, O. An Abridgement of the Quarto Edition of Ainsworth’s Dictionary, English and Latin, &c. by Thomas Morrell, L. L. D. London, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ascham, 195, O. The Scholemaster: shewing a plain and perfect way of teaching the learned Languages. By Roger Aschani, Esq. Preceptor to Queen Elizabeth. Revised and improved by James Upton, A. M., &c. London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bachmair, 211, O. A German Grammar, containing the Theory of the Language, through all the Parts of Speech, &c. &c. By John James Bachmair, M. A. Philad. 1788.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bentzius, 69, F. Thesaurus Elocutionis Oratoriae Græcolatinus Novus, &c. a M. Joanne Bentzio, Bruxellense. Basileae, 1581.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Blount, 99, F. Censura celebriorum Authorum, sive Tractatus in quo Varia Virorum Doctorum de Clarissimis cujusque Seculi Scriptoribus judicia traduntur, &c. &c. Omnia in Studiosorum gratiam collegit, &c, Thomas Pope Blount, Anglo-Britannus, Baronettus.—Londini, 1690.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Brutus, 330, O. Joh. Michaelis Bruti Opera varia selecta, nimirum Epistol. Lib. V. de Historiae Laudibus, sive de Ratione legendi Scriptores historicos liber, Praeceptorum Conjugalium liber, Epistolis et Orationibus compluribus. Berolini, 1698.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Calepinus, 34, F. Ambrosii Calepini Dictionarium, tanta tamque multa verborum, tum Latinorum, tum etiam Graecorum, quae suis Latinis bellissimè respondent, loquendique formularum accessione adauctum, ut thesaurus Linguae Latinae dici possit. Adjunctae sunt praeterea singulis</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vocibus Latinis, Italicae, Gallicæ, et Hispanicae interpretationes, &c. &c. &c. Praeterea subjuncta sunt, Pauli Manutii, Aldi F. Additamenta, &c. &c. &c.—   Lutetiae, 1570.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Calepinus, 72, F. Ambrosii Calepini Dictionarium Linguarum septem. Quo respondent Latinis vocabulis, Graeca, Italica, Gallica, Hispanica, Germanica, Belgica; praefixi sunt Tres Indices Alphabetici, in quibus, Hebraicae, Latinae et Germanicae dictiones, mutatis vicibus, sibi mutuò respondent. Item, Onomasticum, etc. &c. Basileae, 1579.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carey, 34, O. A Work in Bengalee. (Presented by W. Carey.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carey, 42, O. A Work in Bengalee. (Presented by W. Carey.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carey,  2, Q. A Grammar of the Sungskrit language, composed from the Works of the most esteemed Grammarians. To which are added, Examples for the Exercise of the Student, and a complete List of the Dhatoos, or Boots. By W. Carey, Teacher of the Sungskrit, Bengalee, and Mahratta Languages. in the College of Fort William. Serampore, 1806. (Presented by the author.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carey, 41, O. Dialogues; intended to facilitate the acquiring of the Bengalee language. By W. Carey. Serampore, 1801. (Presented by the author.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carré, 8, D. Traité complet de la Prononciation de la Langue Anglaise, &c. par Charles Carré. Philad. 1818.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cellarius, 51, D. Christophori Cellarii, Smalcaldiensis, Curae posteriores de Barbaraismis et Idiotismis Sermonis Latini, secundum secula distributae. Cizae, 1681.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cellarius, 52, D. The same work. Jenae, 1700.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chamberlayne, 129, Q. Oratio Dominica in diversas omnium fere Gentium Linguas versa et propriis cujusque Linguae Charasteribus expressa, una cum Dissertationibus nonnullis de Linguarum Origine, variisque ipsarum Permutationibus, Editore Joanne Chamberlaynio, F. R. S., &c. Amstelodami, 1715.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clericus, 345, O. Joannis Clerici Ars Critica; cum Epistolis Criticis et Ecclesiasticis. Tom. 3. Amstelodami, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clenardus, 321, O. Institutiones Linguae Græca, N. Clenardo, authore. Cum Scholiis et Praxi P. Antesignani Rapistagnensis. Coloniae, 1569.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dasypodius, 47, O. Lexicon Graecolatinum in usum juventutis</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Græcarum literarum studiosae, diligenter congestum; opera Petri Dasypodii. Argentorati, 1539.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>De-Rossi. 5, Q. Annales Hebræo-Typographici Sec. XV. descripsit, fusoque Commentario illustravit Joh. Bernardus De-Rossi, Ling. Orient. Profess. Parmae, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Eliot, 76 —4, O. A Grammar of the Massachusetts Indian Language. By John Eliot. With Notes and Observations, by Peter S. Du Ponceau,LL. D. and an Introduction and Supplementary Notes, by John Pickering. Boston, 1822.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 67, D. Querela Pacis undique gentium ejectae, profligataeque.—Encomium Moriae, sive Declamatio in laudem Stultitiae.—De ratione studiorum libellus.—De ratione instituendi Discipulos.—De utraque Verborum ac Rerum Copia libri II. ad sermonem et stylum formandum utilissimi.—Omnia a Desiderio Erasmo Roterodamo Scripta. Lugduni Batavorum et Amstelodami, 1641—1645.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 75, D. Desiderii Erasmi Roter. Liber utilissimus de conscribendis Epistolis; continens artificium et praecepta in earum compositione observanda. Amstelo- dami, 1636.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Faber, Tan. 257, O. A Compendious Way of teaching Ancient and Modern Languages, as practised by Tanaquil Faber, &c. with Observations by Ascham, Carew, Wilton, Locke, &c. & c. By J. T. Philipps. London, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Francius 342, O. Petri Francii Eloquentiae exterioris specimen primum, ad Orationem M. T. Ciceronis pro A. Licin. Archia accommodatum. Amstelodami, 1700.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Franklin 42, D. De Linguae Græcæ Tonis Tractatulus. R. Franklino Autore. Edidit Jac. Richardson, A. M., &c. Londini, 1717.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grammatica, 17. D. Brevissima Institutio seu ratio Grammatices cognoscendae, etc. &c. Oxonii, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grammatica Graeca, 327, O. Græcæ Grammatices Rudimenta. In usum Scholæ Regiæ Westmonasteriensis. Londini, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Guignes, de 11, F. Dictionnaire Chinois, Français et Latin, publié d&apos;apres l&apos;ordre de S. M. l&apos;Empereur et Roi Napoléon le grand; par M. de Guignes, Resident de France à la Chine,&c. &c. a Paris, 1813.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Harris, 240, O. Hermes; or, a Philosophical Inquiry concerning Language and Universal Grammar. By James Harris. London, 1751.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hedericus, 105, O. Benjamin Hederici Lexicon Minuale Latino-Germanicum, &c. &e. &c. Cum Compendiorum Scripturæ Signorumque, &c. &c. Ilterpretatione, &c. &c. Tom. 2. Lipsiæ, 1766.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Howison, 26, Q. A Dictionary of the Malay Tongue, as spoken in Malacca, Java, Borneo, &c. &c. With a Grammar of that Language. By James Howison, M. D. Map. London, 1801.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Johnson, 19, F. Dictionary of the English Language: in which the words are deduced from their originals, and illustrated in their different significations by example from the best Writers, &c. & c. &c. By Samuel Johnson, A. M. 2 vols. London, 1755.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ker, 247. O. Selectarum de Lingua Latina Observationum libri duo. Ductu et Cura Joannis Ker. Tom. I. Londini, 1709.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Leusden, 126, Q. Philologus Hebraeus, in quo pleræque quaestiones generales philologico-hebraicae, concernentes Textum Hebraeum Veteris Testamenti dilucidè pertractantur. Cum Catalogo hebraico et latino sexcentorum et tredecim Praeceptorum, in quo totus Pentateuchus ex sententiâ Judaeorum divisus est. Authore Joanne Leusden, M. A. &c. Ultrajecti, 1657.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Manutius, 281, O. Adagia optimorum utriusque Linguae Scriptorum omnia, quaecunque ad hunc usque diem exierunt. Pauli Manutii Studio, &c. &c. &c. Ursellis, 1603.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Miege, 54, F. The Great French and English Tictionary, according to the ancient and Modern Orthography with Grammars, Lc. &c. dc. By Guy Miege, Gent. London, 1688.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Moor, 184, O. Elementa Linguae Græcae; novis, plerumque, Regulis tradita, &c. &c. Studio Jacobi Moor, LL. D. &c. Edinburgi, 1798.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Morrison, 1, Q. A Dictionary of the Chinese language, &c. &c. By the Rev. R. Morrison. Vol. 1. part 1. Macao, 1815.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Morrison, 20, Q. A Grammar of the Chinese language. By the Rev. Robert Morrison. Serampore, 1815.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mosellanus, P. 341, O. Annotationes Petri Mosellani Protogensis in clarissimas Auli Gellii Noctes Atticas.—Plutarchus Chæron. de educatione puerorum. Graece.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Epistola Erasmi de modestia profitendi Linguas.- Libellus D. Joannis Chrysostomi de Babyla martyre Græce. — Epistola Erasmi in tyrologum quendam impudentissimum calumniatorem. Basileae, 1527.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Neandrus, 316, O. Graecae Linguae Erotemata. Michaele Neandro, Soraviensi autore. Basileae, 1576.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nizolius, 77, F. Nizolius sive Thesaurus Ciceronianus, post Mar. Nizolii, Basilii, Zanchi, et Caelii Secundi Curionis, nunquam satis laudatas operas, per Marcellum Squarcialupum Plumbinensem, cum insigni accessione, digestus et illustratus. Basileae, 1576.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ortelius, 85, Q. Abrahami Ortelii, Antverpiani, Synonymia Geographica, sive Populorum, Regionum, Insularum, Urbium, &c. & c. &c, variae, pro Auctorum traditionibus, saeculorum intervallis, gentiumque idiomatis et migrationibus, appellationes et nomina. Antverpiae, 1578.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Parkhurst, 28, Q. An Hebrew and English Lexicon, without Points, &c. &c. Also a Methodical Hebrew Grammar, without Pointe, &c. &c. By John Parkhurst, M. A. &c. London, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ruddimannus, 303, O. Grammaticae Latinae Institutiones. Thomae Ruddimanno, A. M. Auctore. Edinburgi, 1746.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sanctius, 155, O. Francisci Sanctii, Brocensis, Minerva; seu de Causis Linguae Latinae Commentarius. Cum Addit. Gasp. Scioppii et Animadversionibus Jac. Perisonii. Amstelodami, 1714.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Scaligerus, 295, O. Julii Cæsaris Scaligeri exotericarum Exercitationum liber XV. de Subtilitate, ad Hieronymum Cardanum. Francofurti, 1576.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Scaligerus, 301, O. The same work. Francofurti, 1601.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schrevelius, 189, O. Lexicon Manuale Græco-Latinum et Latino-Græcum. A Cornelio Schrevelio editum, &c. &c. Londini, 1699.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schrevelius,  125, O. The same work. Augustæ apud Vindelicos, 1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Scot, 69 Q. Apparatus Latinæ Locutionis, in usum studiosae juventutis: post Marii Nizolii Principia ex M. T. Ciceronis libris collectus. Auctore Alexandro Scot, Scoto, A. M. &c. Accessit ad calcem Progymnasma tum in artem oratoriam libellus, ex Francisci Sylvii opere in Synopsim redactus. Lutetiae Parisiorum, 1622.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sewel, 39. Q. A Large Dictionary, English and Dutch, &c. With a Grammar for both Languages. &c. &c. By W. Sewel. 2 vols. Amsterdam, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sobrino 73. Q. Dicionario Nuevo de las Lenguas Española y Francesa; en que se contiene la explicacon del Espanol al Francès, y del Francès aI Espanol, &c. &c. Por Don Francisco Sobrino. 2 tom. En Brusselas, 1721.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Steenberch, Van, 349, O. Vera ac Genuina cognoscendi Methodus studiosae Juventuti praescripta ab Elia Van Steenberch, Phil. Doct. &c. Daventriæ, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stuart, 5, O. A Hebrew Grammar, with a copious Syntax and Praxis. By Moses Stuart. Andover, 1821.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stubelius, 270, O. M. Andr. Stubelii, Graecismus in Nuce; sive aureum inventum Grammaticae Graecae accuratissimae, &c. &c &c. Londini, 1716.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vossius, &c. 109, Q. Disquisitiones Criticae de variis per diversa Loca et Tempora Bibliorum Editionibus. Quibus accedunt Castigationes Theologi cujusdum Parisiensis ad opusculum Isa. Vossii de Sibyllinis Oraculis, et ejusdem Responsionem ad objectiones nuperae criticae sacrae. Londini, 1684.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vossius, &c. 134, Q. Gerardi Joannis Vossii de Veterum Poetarum Temporibus libri duo, qui sunt de Poetis Graecis et Latinis. Amstelodami, 1654.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vossius, &c. 135, Q. Gerardi Joannis Vossii duo Tractatus Aurei, Unus de Historicis Latinis, Alter de historicis Graecis. Cum effigie. Francofurti ad Moenum, 1677. (Presented by Lewis Evans.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Walker, 14, D. A New Dictionary of English Paricles, with a Praxis upon the same. By William Walker, B. D.— London, 1706.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Walker, 300, O. A Treatise of English Particles, &c. &c. With a Praxis upon the same. By William Walker, B. D.— London, 1691.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Walker, 45, O. A Key to the Classical Pronunciation of the Greek, Latin, and Scripture proper names, &c.&c. &c. By John Walker. Philadelphia, 1808.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ward, 273, O. A System of Oratory, delivered in a course of Lectures publicly read at Gresham College, London; with an Inaugural Oration in Latin, &c. &c: By John Ward, LL. D., &c. 2 vols. London, 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Willymott, 242, O. The Peculiar Use and Signification of certain Words in the Latin Tongue, &c. &c, By William Willymott, M. A. &c. Cambridge, 1705.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wilson, 121, O. An Essay on Grammar; the Principales of which are exemplified and appended in an English Grammar. By James P. Wilson, D. D. Philadelphia, 1817. (Presented by the author.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wolfius, 119, F. Hieronymi Wolfiii in Ciceronis officia, Catonem, Lælium, Paradoxa, et Scipionis Somnium Commentarii atque Scholia, ad vitam rectè instituendam, methodumque Scholarum exercendam, accommodata. Basileae, 1584.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Adam’s, 185, O. A Greatise on the construction and Use of new Celestial and Terrestrial /Globes, &c. &c. By George Adams. Plates. London, 1766.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Almanac&apos; Nautical, &c. 82, O. The Nautical Almanac and Astronomical Ephemeris for the years 1767, 8, 9, 70, (with Martin’s Institutions of Astronomical Calculations.— Tables de la Lune, &c. par M. Elairaut.—Tables, requisite to be used with the Astronomical and Nautical Ephemeris, &c. &c.) 1771, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, &apos;80, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, &apos;90. (Cum Tabulis pro supputandis Eclipsibus Secundi Satellitis Jovis: auctore D. Wargentin, &c.—Description of a method for adjusting Hadley’s Quadrant, &c. by R. Blair.—Edwards on Reflecting Telecopes.— Right Ascessions and Zenith Distances of the Moon, deduced from Dr. Gradley’s Observations, &c. Lyons’s Astronomical Problems.) 1791, 96, 97, 99, 1802, 3, 4. London—V. Y.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristolle, 60, Q. Commentarii Collegii Conimbricensis Societatis Jesu, in Quatuor libros de Cœlo, Meteorologicos et Parva Naturalia, Aristotelis Stagiritæ. Coloniae, 1603.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bailly, 56, Q. Histoire de l’Astronomie Moderne, depuis la fondation de l’ecole d’Alexandrie jusqu’à l&apos;epoque de 1782. Por M. Bailly. Time 3me. a Paris, 1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Belidor, 16, D. Le Bombardier François, ou Nouvelle Methode de jetter les Bombes avec précision. Par M. Belidor. Avec figures. A Paris, 1731.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bezout, 350, O. Elementos de Analyse por Mr. Bezont, traduzidos de Francez. Tom. II. Coimbra, 1801.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boyle, 313, O. experimenta, Observationes, &c. circa Mechanicam variarum particularium Qualitatum Originem sive Productionem. Accessit Tractatus, quo Chymistanum de Qualitatibus Doctrinae Imperfectio detegitur. Necnon quaedam in Hypothesin de Alcali et Acido Animad versiones. Authorto Boylæo Roberto, Armigero, R. Soc. Socio. Londini, 1692.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Beaumont. 99—1, Q. Considerations on a Book, entitled, The Theory of the Earth, publisht some years since by the  learned Dr. Burnet. By John Beaumont, Jun. London, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cellarius, 88, O. Christophori Cellarii Smalcaldiensis Geographia Antiqua. Curà Samuelis Patrick,LL. D. Londini, 1808.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Celius, 129—2, O. Andreæ Celsii Oratio de Mutationibus generalioribus quae in superficie Corporum Coelestium contingunt. Lugduni Batavorum, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chabert, 54, Q. Voyage fait par ordre du Roi, en 1750 et 1751, dans l&apos;Amerique Septentrionale, pour rectifier les Cartes des Côtes de l&apos;Acadie,de l&apos;Isle Royale et de l’Isle de Terreneuve; et pour en fixer les principaux points par des Observations Astronomiques. Par M. de Chabert. Avec Cartes, &c. Paris, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clare, 233, O. The Moation of Fluids, Natural and Artificial, in particular that of the Air and Water, with Experiments, &c. & c. &c. By M. Clare, F. R. S. &e. Plates.— London, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clericus, 356, O. Joannis Clerici Physica, sive de Rebus Corporeis Libri quinque. Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1698.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cotes, 165, O. HydrostaticaI and Pneumatic Lectures, by Roger Cotes, A. M. &c. The second edition. By Robert Smith, D. D. &c. Plates. Cambridge, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cotes, 77, Q. Harmonia Mensurarum, sive Analysis et Synthesis per Rationum et Angulorum Mensuras promotae: accedunt alia Opuscula Mathematica: per Rogerum Cotesium. Edidit et auxit Robertus Smith, Astr. &c. Prof. Cantabrigiæ, 1722.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Courtanvaux, 55, Q. Journal du Voyage de M. le Marquis de Courtanvaux, sur le frégate l’Aurore, pour essayer par ordre de l&apos;Académie, plusieurs Instrumens relatifs à la Longitude. Mis en ordre par M. Pingré, nommé par l&apos;Académie pour coopérer à la verification desdits In strumens, de concert avec M. Messier, Astronome de la Marine. Avec figures. A Paris, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Des-Cartes, 102, Q. Renati Des-Cartes Principia Philosophiae. Amstelodami, apud L. Elzevirium, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>De Dimensione, §c. 120—1, Q. De dimensione quarundam superficierum curvilinearium, ac corporum inde genitorum, &c. &c. &c. Bambergae, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ellicott, 40, Q. The Journal of Andrew Elliott, late Commissioner on behalf of the United States during part of the year 1796, the years 1797, 1798, 1799, and part of 1800, for détermining the Boundary between the United Stats and the Possessions of his Catholic Majesty in  America, containing Remacks on the Situation, Soil, Rivers, Natural Productions, and Diseases of the different Countries on the Ohio, Mississippi, and Gulf of Mexico. With six Maps, and an Appendix. Philadelphia, 1803.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Emerson, 75, Q. The Principales of Mechanics, &c. &c. &c., By William Emerson. With 43 copperplates. London, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Emerson, 134. 0. The Elements of Trigonometry. By William Emerson. Plates. London, 1749.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Eucid, 228, O. Euclidis Elementorum libri priores sex, item, undecimus et duodecimus. Ex Versione Latina Federici Commandini. Quibus accedunt Trigonometriae planae et sphericae Elementa. Item, Tractatus de Natura et Arithmetica Logarithmorum. Oxonii, 1723.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Eucid, 214, O. Euclid’s Element of Geometry, from the Latin translation of Commandine. With Treatises on Arithmetic and Trigonometry, &c. &c. By Dr. John Keil, F. R. S. &c. Revised, &c. &c. &c. by Samuel Cunn.- London, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ewing, 56, O. A Plain Elementary and Practical System of Natural and Experimental Philosophy; including Astronomy and Chronology. By the late Rev. John Ewing, D. D. &c. With Notes, &c, by Robert Patterson, Prof. &c. and the Life of the Author. Plates. Philadelphia, 1809.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ferguson, 32, Q. Astronomy explained upon Sir Isaac Newton’s Principles, and made easy to those who have not studied Mathematics. By James Ferguson. Plates. London, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ferguson, 33, Q. The same Work.—To which are added, A plain  Method of finding the Distances of all the Planets from the Sun, by the transit of Venus over the Sun’s disc in 1761.—An account of Mr. Hor prox’s Observation of the Transit of Venus in 1639; and of the Distances of all the Planets from the Sun, as deduced from Observations of the Transit in 1761. London, 1764.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Flamsteed, 3, F. Atlas Coelestis. By the late Rev. Mr. John Flamsteed, Regius Professor of Astronomy at Greenwich. Portrait. London, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gardiner 10, Q. Tables of Logarithms, for all numbers from 1 to 102100, and for the Sines and Tangents to every ten seconds of each degree in the Quadrant; as also, for the Sines of the first 72 minutes to every single second: with other useful and necessary Tables. By William Gardiner. London, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>s&apos;Gravesande, 7, D. G. J. s’Gravesande, Philosophiae Newtonianae Institutiones, in Usus Academicos. Lugduni Batavorum, 1723.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>S&apos;Gravesande, 79, Q. Mathematical Elements of Natural Philosophy, confirmed by Experiments: or, an Introduction to Sir Isaac Newton’s Philosophy. written in Latin by the late W. James s&apos;Gravesande, LL. D., F. R. S. &c.— Translate into English by the late J. T. Desaguliers, LL. D., F. R. S. With 127 copper-plates. 2 vols.— London, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gray, 244, O. A Testise of Gunnery. By John Gray. London, 1731.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Greene, 63, F. The Principles of the Philosophy of the Expansive and Contractive Forces. Or, an Inquiry into the Principles of the Modern Philosophy; that is, into the Several Chief Rational Sciences, which are extant. By Robert Greene, M. A. &c. Cambridge, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gregory, 58, F. Astronomiae Physicae et Geometricae Elementa. Auctore Davide Gregorio, M. D. Astron. Prof. Savil. Ononiæ, &c. Oxoniae, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Guttenberg, de 120—5, Q. De Sectionibus Conicis, &c. Auct. D. P. T. L. B. de Guttenberg. Bambergæ, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hamilton, 29, Q. De Sectionibus Conicis, Tractatus Geometricus; in quo ex Natura ipsius Coni Sectionum Affectiones facillime deducuntur; Methodo Nova. Auctore Hugone Hamilton, A. M. &c. Londini, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hammond, 130, O. The Practical Surveyor, &c. &e.&c. By John Hammond and Samuel Werner. Plates. London, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hassler, 30, O. Element of Analytic Trigonometry, plane and spherical. By F. R. Hassler, F. A. P. S. New York, 1826. (Presented by P. S. Du Ponceau, Esq.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hauy, 85, O. An Elementary Treatise on Natural Philosophy. Translated from the French of M. R.-J. Haüy, Prof. of Minerology, &c. By Olinthus Gregory, A. M. &c., With notes by the Translator. Plates. 2 vols. London, 1807.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hesham, 167, O. A Course of Lectures on Natural Philosophy. By the late Richard Helsham, M. D. &c. published by Bryan Robinson, M. D. Plates. London, 1739.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hesham, 205, O. The same Work. Philadelphia, 1802.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hugenius, 100, Q. Christiani Hugenii Zelemii, dum viveret,  Toparchae, Opuscula Postuma, quae continent Dioptricam. Commentarios de Vitris figurandis. Dissertationem de Corona et Parheliis. Tractatum de Motu, de Vi Centrifuga. Descriptionem Automati Planetarii. Cum figuris. Lugduni Batavorum, 1703.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jæger, 120—6, Q. Schemæ Exercitationis Mathematicae in Arithmaticam, Algebram, ad usus domesticos, &c. applicatus, &c. &c &c. Auctore J. Jæger. Bambergæ, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kastner, 75, O. Einleitung in die neuere Chemie, Behufs seiner Vorlesungen und zum Selbstunterrichte für Aufänger herausgegeben. Von C. W. G. Kästner, M. D. &c.— Halle, 1814.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Keill, 267, O. introductio ad veram Physicam: seu Lectiones physicae habitae in Schola Naturalis Philosophiae Academiae Oxoniensis, quibus accedunt Christiani Hugenii Theoremata de Vi Centrifuga, et Motu Circulari demonstrata, per Jo. Keill, A. M. &c. Oxoniae, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kelly, 231, O. The modern Navigation’s compleat Tutor: or, A Treatise of the whole Art of Navigation in its theory and Practice, &c. &c. &c. By Joshua Kelly. 2 vols. London, 1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lamy, 31, D. Elemens des Mathematiques, ou Traité de la Grandeur en general, etc. &c. par le R. P. Bernard Lamy. A Paris, 1704.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Leadbetter, 163, O New Tables of the Motions of the Planets, the fixed Stars, and the first Satellite of Jupiter; of Right and Oblique Ascensions and Logistical Logarithms. By Charles Leadbetter. Vol. II. Lond. 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Le Gentil, 47, Q. Voyage dans les Mers de l&apos;Inde, fait par ordre du Roi, a l&apos;occasion du Passage de Venus, sur le Disque du Soleil, le 6 Juin, 1761, et le 3 du même mois 1769. Par M. Le Gentil, de l’Academie Royale des Sciences. Avec figures. Tom. 2. A Paris, 1779.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Linnaeus 129—1, O. Caroli Linnaei Oratio de Telluris habitabilis incremento. Lugduni Batavorum, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Luders, 6, F. Traicté Mathematique; contenant les principales Definitions, &c. d&apos;Euclide, l&apos;Arithmetique decimale, la Trigonometrie, la Longimetrie, Ia Planimetrie et Stereometrie, la Fortification Hollandoise, Françoise, Italienne et Espagnole, la Perspective militaire, et la Geographie Universelle: par Theodore Luders. A Paris, 1680.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ludlam, 52, Q. Astronomical Observations made at St. John&apos;s  College, Cambridge, in 1767 and 1768: with an Account of several Astronomical Instrument. By the Rev. Mr. Ludlam. Plates. Cambridge, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mac Laurin, 93, Q. A Treatise of Fluxions. By Colin Mac Laurin, A. M., F. R. S. &c. Plates. 2 vols. Edinburg, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Macquer, 123, O. Elements of the Theory and Pracice of Chymistry. Translated from the French of M. Macquer. Vol. II. London, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mairan, 46, Q. Traité physique et historique de l&apos;Aurore Boréale. Par M. de Mairan. Suite des Mémoires de l&apos;Académie Royale des Sciences, Année. 1731. Avec figures. A Paris, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mathematici Veteres, 15, F. Veterum Mathematicorum Athenaei, Apollodori, Philonis, Bitonis, Heronis et Aliorum Opera, Græce et Latine, pleraque nunc primum edita. Ex MSS. Codd. Bibliothecæ Regis. Parisiis, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mathematiques, &c. 50, F. Divers Ouvrages de Mathematique et de Physique. Par MM. de l&apos;Academie Royale des Sciences. A Paris, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Miller, 97, D. Elements of Natural Philosophy. By George Miller, D. D., &c. Plates. Dublin, 1799.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Muller, 119—3, Q. De justo Probabilitatis valore et usu, &c. Auctore P. L. S. Muller. Erlangæ, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Musschenbroek, 104, O. The Elements of Natural (Philosophy). By Peter Van Musschenbroek, M. D. Translated trom the Latin by John Colson, M. A. &c. Vol. I. London, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Musschenbroek, 31, Q. introductio ad Philosophiam Naturalem. Auctore Petro Von Musschenbroek. Cum figuris. Tom. 2.— Lugduni Batavorum, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Newton, 80, Q. Philosophiae Naturalis Principia Mathematica; Auctore Isaaco Newtono, Eq. Aurato. Cum effigie.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Newton, 70, Q. Philosophiae Naturalis Principia Mathematica; Auctore Isaaco Newtono, Eq. Aurato; perpetuis Commentariis illustrata, communi studio PP. Thomae Le Seur et Francisci Jacquier, ex Gallicana Minimorum Familia, Matheseos Professorum. Tom. 3. Coloniae Allobrogum, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Newton, 171, O. The Mathematical Principales of Natural Philosophy. By Sir Isaac Newton. Translated into English by Andrew Motte. With the Laws of the Moon&apos;s Motion, according to Gravity; by John Machin, Astron. Prof. &c. Plates. 2 vols. London, 1729.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Newton, 246, 0. Optice: sive de Reflexionibus, Refractionibus, Inflexionibus et Coloribus Lucis, libri tres. Authore Isaaco Newtono, Eq. Aurato. Latine reddidit Samuel Clarke, S. T. P. Londini, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Newton, 15, Q. A View of Sir Isaac Newton’s Philosophy. By Henry Pemberton, Plates. London, 1728. (Presented by John McDowell.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ozanam. 282, O. Cursus Mathematicus: or, a complete Course of Mathematicks. Vol. II. Containing Arithmetic and Trigonometry. With Tables, &c. &c. Translated from the French of M. Ozanam. London, 1712.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ozanam. 138, 0. Cours de Mathematique. Par M. Ozanam. Tomes 2, 3, 4, 5. A Paris, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Patterson, 91, O. A Brief Outline of Physics, or Natural Philosophy: being an Appendix to Adams’s Lectures, &c. By Robert Patterson. Philadelphia, 1807.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Priestley, 49, Q. The tistory of the present State of Discoveries relating to Vision, Light, and Colours. By Joseph Priestley, LL. D., F. R. S. Plates. London, 1772. (Presented by Dr. Franklin.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rohault, 210, O. Jacobi Rohaulti Physica, Latine vertit, recensuit, Adnotationibus ex illustr. Isaaci Newtoni Philosophia maximam partem haustis amplificavit et ornavit Samuel Clarke, S. T. P. Cum tabulis ære incisis.- Londini, 1718.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rohault, 204, O. Rohault’s System of Natural Philosophy, illustrated with Dr. Samuel Clarke’s Notes, taken mostly out of Sir Isaac Newton’s Philosophy. Done into English by John Clarke, D. D., &c. Plates. 2 vols. London, 1735.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Roppelt, 120—2, Q. Einige Bemerkungen über die praktische Geometrie von J. Roppelt. Ein Programm, &c. &c.; Bamberg, 1794.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Roppelt, 139—6, Q. De Apparatu et Usu Gnomonis geodaetici seu Norma Mensorum, &c. &c. &c. Auctore D. G. J. Roppelt. Bambergæ, 1781.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rutherforth, 48, Q. A System of Natural Philosophy, being a course of Lectures on Mechanics, Optics, Hydrostatics, and Astronomy; which are read in St. John’s College, Cambridge. By T. Rutherforth, D. D., F. R. S., &c. Plates. 2 vols. Cambridge, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Saint Remy, 62, Q. Memoires d’Artillerie, recueillis par le Sr. Surirey de Saint Remy, Commissaire Provincial de l&apos;Artillerie, &c. Avec plusieurs figures. 2 tom. A Paris, 1697, (Presented by Lewis Evans.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ships, working of, &c. 278, O. The theory of the Handling or Working of Ships at Sea. Translated from the French. Plates. London.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sciences, Academie Royale des, 44, F. Recueil d’Observations faites en plusieurs Voyages par ordre de sa Majesté, pour perfectionner l&apos;Astronomie et la Geographie. Avec divers Traitez Astronomiques. Par MM. de l&apos;Academie Royale des Sciences. A Paris, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Simpson, 150, O. The Doctrine and Application of Fluxions. Containing (besides what is common on the subject) a number of new Improvements in the Theory, Solutions, &c. &c. &c. By Thomas Simon, F. R. S. 2 vols. London, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Simpson, 84. Q. Miscellaneous Tracts on some curious, and very interesting subjects in Mechanics, Physical Astronomy, and Speculative Mathematics; wherein, the precession of the Equinox, the Mutation of the Earth’s Axis, and the Motion of the Moon in her Orbit, are determined. By Thomas Simpson, F. R. S. &c. Plates. Lond. 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Simpson, 86, Q. Mathematical Dissertations on a variety of Physical and Analytical subjects. By Thomas Simpson.— London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Simson, R. 90, Q. Sectionum Conicarum libri quinque. Auctore Roberto Simson, M. D., &c. Cum figuris. Edin. 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Smith, 76—1, O. A Dissertation on the General Properties of Eclipses, and particularly that of 1748. By George Smith, Esq. London, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Starrat, 186, O. The doctrine of Projectiles demonstrated and applied to all the most useful problems in Nautical Gunnery. With the Description of a New Mathematical Instrument, &c.&c. By William Starrat. Plates. Dublin, 1733.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stenglein, 120—7, Q. Specimen Praxeon Geometricarum Campestrium, &c. &c., &c., Auctore G. F. X. Stenglein.— Bambergæ, 1769.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stewart, 188, O. Propositiones Geometricae, more Veterum demonstratae, ad Geometriam Antiquam illustrandam et promovendam idoneae. Auctore Matthaeo Stewart, S. T. D. &c. Edinburgi, 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stewart, 124, O. Tracts, Physical and Mathematical. Containing an Explication of several important Points in Physical Astronomy; and a new method for ascertaining the Sun’s distance from the Earth, by the Theory of Gravity. By Dr. Matthew Stewart, Prof. Math. &c. Edinb. 1761.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sreete, 95, Q. Astronomia Carolina: a new Theory of the Celestial Motions.  With Tables, &c. &c. By Thomas Streete. Also, Lunar and Planetary Observations, &c. London, 1710.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Switzer, 67, Q. An Introduction to a General System of Hydrostaticks and Hydraulicks, Philosophical and Practical. Wherein the Methods of raising and conducting Water, &c. &c. are carefully laid down. With Descriptions of Engines, &c.&c. &c. 60 Copperplates. By Stephen Switzer. 2 vols. in 1. London, 1729.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tacquet, 332, O. Andreae macquet Soc. Jesu Matheseos Prof.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Arithmeticae Theoria et Praxis. Amstelodami. 1704.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theses, Philosophical, 145—6, Q. Theses Philosophicae, selectiores ex Physica Experimentali et Mathesi, &c. &c. &c. Fuldae, 1765.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Value, 9 D. Arithmetic, theoretical and practical, &c. &c. By Victor Value. Part I. Philadelphia, 1823.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vossius, 130, Q. Isaaci Vossii de Motu Marium et Ventorum Liber. Hagæ-Comitis, 1663.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wales, 76—3, O. The Method of finding the Longitude at Sea, by Time-Keepers: With Tables of Equations, &c. &c. By William Wales, F. R. S. &c. London, 1800.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ward, 241, O. The Young Mathematician’s Guide: being a plain and easy Introduction to the Mathematics. By John Ward. With a Supplement, &c. Lond. 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Webber, 86, O. Mathematics, compiled from the best Authors, &c. &c. By Samuel Weber, A. M., &c. Vol. II. Boston, 1801.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wells, 38. O. Elementa Arithmeticae Numerosae et Speciosae. Auctore E. Wells. Oxoniae, 1698.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>West, 99, O. Elements of Mathematics. Comprehending Geometry, Conic Sections, Mensuration, Spherics. For the use of Schools. By John West. Plates. Edinburg, 1784.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Whiston, 191, O. Astronomical Lectures, read in the public schools of Cambridge. By William Whiston, M. A., &c. With a collection of Astronomical Tables; being those of Mr. Flamsteed, corrected; Dr. Halley; M. Cassini; and Mr. Street. London, 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Williams, 17, Q. An Account of the Trigonometrical Survey carried on the years 1791, 1792, 1793, and 1794, by order of His Grace the Duke of Richmond, late Master General of the Ordnance. By Lieut. Col. Edward Williams, Captain William M Judge, and Mr. Isaac Dalby. Plates. Read before the Royal Society, June 25, 1795. London.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Winkler 172, O. Element of Natural Philosophy delineated. By John Henry Winkler, F. R. S., &c. Translated from the German. Plates. 2 vols. London, 1757</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wright, 79, O. Elements of Trigonometry, Plane and Spherical: with the Principles of Perspective and Projection of the Sphere. By John Wright. Edinburg, 1772. (Presented by the author.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Young, 68, O. Anarelysis of the Principles of Natural Philosophy. By Matthew Young, D. D., &c. now Bishop of Clonfert. Dublin, 1800.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Acts and Statutes, &c. 123, F. Acts and Statues made in a Parliament begun at Dublin Nov. 12, A. D. 1715. In the second year of King George I., &c. &c. Dublin, 1716.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Addison, 52—5, O. Trial of Judge Addison, reported by Lloyd. Lancaster, 1803.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Andrews, 136, Q. An Apologie for certeine proceedings in Courts Ecclesiasticall. —Item, Quæstionis; Nunquid per Jus Divinum Magistratui liceat a Reo Jusjurandum exigere, &c. &c. Theologica Determinatio. Per Lancelotum. Andrews, S. T. D. — 1591.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristotle, 96, Q. D. Francisci Toleti Soc. Jesu Commentaria, una cum Quæstionibus in tres libros Aristotelis de Anima. Coloniae Agrippinae, 1583.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristotle, 61, Q. Commentarii Collegii Conimbricensis Societatis Jesu, in libros de Generatione et Corruptione Aristotelis Stagiritæ. Moguntiae, 1615.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristotle, 74, Q. Commentarii Collegii Conimbricensis Societatis Jesu, in tres Libros de Anima, Aristotelis Stagiritae. — Coloniae Agrippinae, 1596.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aristotle, 92, Q. D. Francisci Toleti Soc. Jesu Commentaria, una cum Quaestionibus in universam Aristotelis Logicam. — Coloniae Agrippinae, 1596.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barth, 122—2, Q. Rigor Moderatus doctrinae Pontificiae circa Usuras, & c. &c. Auctore F. J. Barth. Ingolstadii, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Baxter 141, O. An Inquiry into the Nature of the human Soul, &c. &c. (by Baxter.) Vol. II. London, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Behr, 125—3, Q. Dissertatlo InaVgVraLIs De IVre & praXI CIrCa saCra In Castro nobILI è trIpLICIs æ VI LapsV In VestIgatIs, &c. &c. Auctore J. A. Behr.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Brandt, 124—6, Q. De Continentia Caussae, &c. &e.&c. Auct. J. F. G. Brandt. Wetzlariae, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Braun, 91—4, Q. Positiones Universales ex Universo Jure, &c. Auctore Jos. G. A. Braun. Bambergae, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Brerewood, 323, O. Tractatus quidam Logici de Praedicabilibus, Praedicamentis, ab Edwardo Brerewood, A. M. &c. Accessere duo ejusdem Authoris insignes Tractatus; prior de Meteoris posterior de Oculo, &c. Oxoniae, 1631.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Breutigamb, 138—4, Q. De Executione in causis Feudalibus, &c. &c. Auctore S. Breutigamb. Bambergae, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Burlamaqui, 128, O. The Principales of Politic Law: being a sequel to the Principales of Natural Law. By J. J. Burlamaqui. Translated into English by Mr. Nugent.- London, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Calvinus. 66, F. Lexicon Juridicum Juris Caesarei simul, et Canonici, Feudalis item, Civilis, Criminalis, theoretici et practici, &c. &c. Accedunt Feudale Lexicon; Leges et Magistratus Roman. &c. &c. &c. Studio et Opera Johannis Calvini, alias Kahl, Wettrani, Juris Doctoris, &c. Cum Praefationibus Gothofredi et Vulteii. Genevæ, 1653.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carpzovius, 97, F. Benedicti Carpzovii, J. U. D. et Cons. Electoris Saxonici Definitiones Ecclesiasticae seu Consistoriales, &c. &c. &c. Accessit usus Arboris Consanguinitatis et Affinitatis in foro Saxon. &c. &c. &c.— Lipsiae, 1708.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chauvinus, 18, F. Lexicon Philosophicum secundis Curis Stephani Chauvini, Philosophiae Professoris, &c. &c. Cum Tabulis aeneis. Leovardiae, 1713.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Corvinus, 62, D. Johannis Am. Corvini, J. C. Enchiridium; seu Institutiones Imperiales insertis latioribus materiis, theoricè, et practicè digestae et explicatae per Erotemata. Amstelodami, 1649.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dangel, 91—1, Q. De eo, quod Jure publico universali circa Collegia, praesertim litteraria, Juris est, &c. &c. Auct. G. A. Dangel. Bambergæ, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Demeradt 124—5, Q. Differentiae Juris Communis et Franconici Petri Rod. Demeradt, &c. &c. &c. Cum notis Leo nardi Curlier, &c. Wirceburgi, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Duane, W. J. 52—1, O. An lnvestigation of the Law of Nations. By W. J. Duane. Philadelphia, 1809.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dumler, 140—2, Q. Certamen Possessorium per Canonico-Legales expositum Contreversias, &c.&c. Auctore G. S. Dümler. Ingolstadii, 1693.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ehrthal, 139—5, Q. Dissertationes Ethicae ex principiis Philosophiae Moralis, et Oraculis Christianorum ac Gentium concinnatae, &c. &c Auct. C. F. W. L. B. ab Ehrhtal. Herbipoli, 1736.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Faber, Basilius, 27, F. Basilii Fabri Sorani Thesaurus Eruditionis Scholasticae, omnium usui et disciplinis omnibus accommodatus, post celeberrimorum virorum Buchneri, Cellarii, Graevii, Operas et Adnotationes et multiplices Andreae Stubelii curas, recensitus, emendatus, locupletatus a Jo. Matthia Gesnero. Lipsiae, 1726.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Friderich, 121—2, Q. Juris Ecclesiastici ad Statum Germaniae adcommodati summa Capita, &c. Auctore P. P. Friderich. Bambergæ, 1789.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gassendus, 46, D. Institutio Logica, et Philosophiæ Epicuri Syntagma. Authore V. Cl. Petro Gassendo. Londini, 1668.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Geilfusius, 352—2, O. Intelligentia, seu primorum Principiorum Habitus, &c. &c. Opera Johannis Geilfusii. Tubingae, 1662.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grove, 164, O. A System of Moral Philosophy, by the late Reverend and Learned Mr. Henry Grove, of Taunton. Published from the Author’s MS. by Thomas Amory. 2 vols. London, 1755.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gutkius, 352—1, O M. Georgii Gutkii Habitus primorum Principionum seu Intelligentiae. Cum Disputationibus, &c. &c. et Additamento Heinzelmani. Berolini, 1661.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Habermann, 145—5, Q. F. Lud. Habermann, Commentarius in Institutiones Juris Civilis, &c. &c. Cum Coroll. D. C. F. L. B. ab Hutten. Herbipoli, 1726.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Habermann, 143—4, Q. F. Lud. Habermann, continuatio Commentarii in Institutiones Juris Civilis, &c. &c. &c. Cum coroll. &c. D. F. J. L. B. de Münster. Herbipoli, 1726.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hanaver, 119—2, Q. Existente alio valore Monetae tempore contractus celebrati, &c. &c, & c. Ac. Auctore F. B. Hanaver. Bambergæ, 1776.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Haysdorff, 125—4, Q. De Reservato Postarum Caesaris proprio, et qua tali a Statibus Imperii agnito, &c. &c. Auctore J. H. Haysdorff. Bambergae, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heineccius, 178, O. A Methodical System of Universal Law: or the Laws of Nature and nations deduced from certain Principles, and applied to proper Cases. Translated from the Latin of Jo. Got. Heineccius, and illustrated with Notes and a Supplement, by George Turnnull, LL. D. With a Discourse on the Nature, &c. of Moral and Civil Laws, &c. &c. 2 vols. London, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grasmannsdorf, de 124—3, Q. De Decimis, &c. &c. &c. Auctore J. F. J. Heinrichen de Grasmannsdorf. Bambergæ, 1761.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Helvetius, 59, Q. De l’Esprit: or, Essays on the Mind, and its several Faculties. Translated from the French of Helvetius. London, 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Herne, 130, F. The Pleader: containing Perfect Presidents and Forms of Declarations, &c. &c, &c. By John Herne. London, 1657.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heyl, 138—2, Q. De Genuino Sensu Paragr. 52. Art. 5. I. P. &c. &c. Auctore C. F. Heyl. Bambergae, 1774.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hogan, 50—6, O. The Trial of the Rev. William Hogan, Pastor of St. Mary’s Church, for an Assault and Battery on Mary Connell, in April, 1822. Philadelphia, 1823.— (Presented by R. De Silver.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Holl, 111—5, Q. De Potestate imperantis circa mutationes ultimarum Voluntatum ut legibus conformium, &c. &c. — Auctore P. J. Holl. Bambergae, 1778.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hunold, 141—2, Q. Theses ex Jure Canonico de Legibus, &c. &c. Auctore D. J. C. Hunold. Bambergae, 1712.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hutcheson, 66, Q. A System of Moral Philosophy; written by the late Francis Hutcheson, LL. D. Professor of Philosophy in the University Glasgow. With some Account of the Life, Writings, and Character of the Author, by the Rev. William Leechman, D. D. &c. 2 vols Glasgow, 1755.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hutcheson, 78, O. An Inquiry into the Original of our Ideas of Beauty and Virtue, &c. By Francis Hutcheson. Lond. 1729.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Intellectus Operationes, &c. 139—4, Q. Intellectus Operationes pro exercitio, &c. &c. &c. Fuldae, 1789.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Isæus, 19, Q. The Speeches of Isæus in causes concerning the Law of the Succession of property at Athens, with a Prefatory Discourse, notes, critical and historical, and a Commentary. By William Jones, Esq. Barister, &c. London, 1779.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Julianus, 51, F. Juliani Imperatoris Opera quae supersunt omnia, et S. Cyrilli, Alexandriae Archiepiscopi, contra impium Julianum libri decem. Accedunt Dionysii Petavii in Julianum Notae, et aliorum aliquot ejusdem Imperatoris libros Praefationes ac Notae. Curâ &c. Ezechielis Spanhemii. Graecè et Latinè. Lipsiae, 1696.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Judex in Judicium, &c. 138—5, Q. Judex in Judicium Scholasticum vocatus, &c. &c. &c. Bambergæ, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jus Canonicum, 33, F. Corpus Juris Canonici Gregorii XIII.  Pont. Max. jussu editum: a Petro Pithoeo, et Francisco Fratre, Jurisonsultis, ad veteres Codices MSS. restitutum et Notis illustratum. Parisiis, 1687.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jus Canonicum, 106, Q. Demonstratio Jurium Status Ecclesiastici circa Temporalia, ex Principiis Juris Naturae potissimum deducta. 1757</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jus Canonicum, 123—2, Q. Corollaria ecclesiastico-juridica hodierno Germaniae Statui accommodata, &c. &c. &c. — Bambergæ, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jus Civile, 250, 0. corpus Juris Civilis, a Dionysio Gothofredo J. C. recognitum, in quo vice interpretationis, variae lectiones, si non omnes, praecipuae tamen, et magis necessariae adjectae. Tom. 2. Lugduni, 1589.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jus Civile, 162, O. Corpus Juris Civilis. Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1700.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kunsberg, 97—5, Q. Dissertatio Juris Germanici, de Renunciationibus Filiarum illustrium, &c. &c. &c. Auctore W. Fr. L. B. de Künsberg. Bambergae, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Laws of Pennsylvania, 107, O. Laws of Pennsylvania, vols. 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10. 1802—1809.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Leisner, 145—3, Q. De Beneficio Divisionis Correis debendi non tributo, &c. &c. Auctore A. Leisner. Bambergae, 1772.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Libertas humana, 111—8, Q. De libertate Humana, &c. Bambergae, 1797.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lindenfels, 119—6, Q. Theses selectae ex universo Jure, &c.— Auctore C. F. L. B. de Lindenfels. Bambergae, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Linheimer, 138—1, Q. De Principe legibus soluto, &c. &c. Auctore J. G. Linheimer. Giessæ, 1737.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lochner, de 111—3, Q. Positiones inaugurales ex universo Jure. Auctore A. F. L. B. de Lochner. Bambergæ, 1794.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Logica, &c. 139—1, Q. Hypomnemata logica, &c. &c. Wirceburgi, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Logica, &c. 120—3, Q. Positiones ex Logica, Metaphysica et Mathesi, &c. &c. &c. Bambergæ, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Logica, &c. 122—7, Q. Logica in Compendium redacta, &c. &c. &c. Herbipoli, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Logique, 37, D. La Logique, ou l’Art de Penser: contenant, outre les Regles communes, plusieurs Observations nouvelles, propres a former le Jugement. A Paris, 1668.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lorber, 138—3, Q. De Legatis et Fidei—Commissis particularibus, &c. &c. Auctore J. T. J. Lorber à Störchen.- Herbipoli, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lorber, 141—3, Q. De Allodio Stante superioritate Statuum territoriali quoad praesumptionem hodie imaginario, &c. &c. &c. Auctore J. C. Lorber à Störchen. Bambergæ, 1749.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lorber, 145—1, Q. De Jure Directorii in Circulo Franconico, &c. &c. &c. Auctore J. C. Lorber à Störchen. Bambergae, 1746.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Loven, 144—1, Q. De Jure Principis Catholici circa Sacra, &c. &c. &c. Auctore C. C. Löven. Bambergæ, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Low, 139 —3, Q. De Recentiorum quarta Mentis operatione sive Methodo, &c. &c. Auctore J. Löw. Bambergae, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Malebranche, 71, F. Father Malebranche his Treatise concerning the search after Truth. With the Author’s Treatise of Nature and Grace, &c. &c. &c. Also a short Discourse upon Lights and Colours, by the same Author. Translated by T. Taylor, M. A. &c. London, 1700.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Montaigne, 79, F. Les Essais de Michel Seigneur de Montaigne. Avec des Annotations en Marge, et la Vie de l&apos;Auteur extraicte de ses propres Escrits. A Paris, 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Montesquieu, 199, O. The Spirit of Laws. Translated from the French of M. de Secondat, Baron de Montesquieu, by Mr. Nugent. 2 vols. London, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Muller, 122—3, Q. De Pedi et Gladii, sive Jurisdictionis Spiritualis, et Temporalis in Episcopatibus Germaniae Connubio &c. &c. Auctore Chr. Müller. Bambergæ.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mulzer, 97—4, Q. De eo, quod circa Communionem Bonorum, &c. &c. justum esse videtur; auctore G. C. Mulzer.— Bambergae, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mulzer, 124—2, Q. De eo, quod circa Communionem Bonorum Dominii translativam inter Conjuges, ex jure Naturae, &c. &c. &c. justum esse videtur, &c. &c. Auctore J. C. Mulzer. Bambergæ, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mulzer, 125—5, Q. Casus selecti ad Quatuor libros Institutionum, &c. &c. &c. Auctore G. C. Mulzer. Bambergæ, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nieser, 122—5, Q. Theses, &c. Juridicæ-Theologicæ, &c. &c.— Auctore, D. N. Nieser. Bambergæ, 1766.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Muyden, van, 355. O. Johannis van Muyden, Compendiosa Pandectarum Tractatio, edita in usum Collegiorum.— Trajecti ad Rhenum, 1695.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Padum, 111—7, Q. Positiones Philosophicae, &c. &c. Auct. D. C. Padum et D. J. Wagner. Bambergæ, 1792.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pflaum, 138—6, Q. De Bonæ Fidei Possessore Fructus consumptos, si exinde locupletior factus, restituente, &c. &c. Auctore M. Pflaum. Bambergae, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Philosophiæ, Ichnographia &c. 111—9, Q. Ichnographia Philosophiae, Critica, &c. Bambergæ, 1796.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Platnerus, 141—4, Q. Super usu Legis Rhodiae de Jactu in Bello terrestri, &c. &c. Auct. F. Platnerus. Lipsiae, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Puls, 111 —4, Q. De Jure eundi in partes in Negotiis circularibus locum non tenente, etc. &c. Auctore G. F. Püls. Bambergæ, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Reid, 55, O. An Inquiry into the Human Mind, on the Principles of Common Sense. By Thomas Reid, D. D. &c. Edinburg, 1764.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Reichard. 146—3, Q. De Differentiis Juris Communis et Franconici, &c &c. &c. Auctore C. B. Reichard. Wirceburgi, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Reider, 119—1, Q. De Consensu feudali definite data, &c. Auct. C. Reider. Bambergæ, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Reindl, 140—1, Q. De Judiciis et Processu Judiciario ad Lib. II. Decretalium Gregorii IX. & c. &c. &c. Auctore P. E. Reindl. Salisburgi, 1723.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ritter, 111—2, Q. De Consensu feudali in genere, et in specie de personis consentientibus, &c. &c. Auctore J. G. Ritter. Bambergæ, 1770.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rutherforth, 149, O. Institutes of Natural Law, being the substance of a Course of Lectures on Grotius de Jure Belli et Pacis, read in St. John’s College, Cambridge, by T. Rutherforth, D. D. F. R. S. &c. 2 vols. Cambridge, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sacheverell, 121, F. The Tryal of Dr. Henry Sacheverell, before the House of Peers, for High Crimes and Misdemeanors, &c. &c. Begun Feb. 27, 1709-10, and continued till March 23d. following. London, 1710.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sanchez, 47, F. R. P. Thomæ Sanchez Cordubensis, e Societate Jesu, de Sancto Matrimonio Sacramento. Cum Constitutionibus SS. D. N. Papae Benedicti XIV. circa idem Sacramentum editis, &c. &c. 3 tom. Viterbii, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schell, 111—6, Q. De Agnato dominove vasalli absentis ut ut Nobilis immediati curatore, &c. &c. &c. Auctore J. M. E. Schell. Bambergae, 1778.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schild, 125—6, Q. Collatio Juris Civilis Romani de Emptione Venditione Fructuum imperfectorum in herbis pendentium cum Ordinatione Topica Fuldensi de quâ Martii 1728, &c. &c. Auctore G. J. Schild. Fuldae, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schlehlein, 111—1, Q. De Stylo et Praejudiciis summorum imperii Tribunalium, &c. Auctore G. A. Schlehlein. Bambergae, 1773.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schmidt, 119—4, Q. Positiones inaugurales ex omnigeno Jure et ejus Historia, &c. Auctore P. Antonius Schmidt. — Bambergæ, 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schmidt, 125—1, Q. De Indole ac Natura Judiciorum Germaniae, &c. &c. &c. Auctore B. Schmidt. Bambergae, 1749.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schmidt, 223, O. Institutiones Juris Ecclesiastici Germaniae adcommodatae. Edidit in usum Auditorum suorum An tonius Schmidt, V. J. D. &c. Tom. 2. Bambergæ, 1778.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schubert, 141—1, Q. Zoesius redivivus, sive Institutionum Imp. Justiniani cum Notis, &c. &c &c liber primus; &c. &c. &c. Auct. J. G. A. Schubert. Wirceburgi, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schuberth, 142—4, Q. De Origine et conditione Ecclesiarum Col- legiatarum in Genere et Ecclesiae Collegiatae ad B. V. M. et S. Gangolphum Bambergæ in Specie, &c.&c. Auct. M. H. Schuberth. Bambergæ, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schuz, 141—7, Q. De Potestatuum Imperii, &c. &c. Auct. B. M. L. B. Schüz ab Holzhausen. Bambergæ, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schwarz. 104, F. Institutiones Juris Universalis, Naturae, et Gentium, &c. &c. &c. Author P. Ignatio Schwarz, S. J. Sacerdote. Augustae, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Selfridge, 31, O. Trial of Thomas P. Selfridge, Counsellor at Law, before the Hon. Isaac Parker, Esq. for killing Charles Austin, on the Public Exchange, Boston, Aug. 4, 1806. Boston, 1809.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Senckenberg, 87, Q. Methodus Jurisprudentiae; ex propriis et peregrinis Juribus Germaniae receptae; aliquibus monimentis anecdotis illustrata. Opus Henrici Christiani Baronis de Senckenberg. Cons. Imp. Aul. Francofurti ad Mœnum, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Seuberth, 138—7, Q. Diss. Inaug. Juridica, &c. &c. ad illust. Capit. Noviss. Art. XIII. § IX. &c. Auct. J. L. Seuberth. Bambergæ, 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Shaftesbury, 20, D. Shadtesbury&apos;s Characteristics, vols. 2 and 3. London, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sondinger, 125—2, Q. De Nobili immediate cum persona Rustica Nuptias contrahente, &c. &c Auct. H. Sondinger. Bambergæ, 1755.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sanley, 58, Q. The History of Philosophy: containing the Lives, Opinions, Actions and Discourses of the Philosophers of every Sect. By Thomas Stanley, Esq. With an Account of his Life and Writings. London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stapff, 143–1, Q. Observationes Juris feudalis Germanici, &c. &c Auct. J. G. Stapff. Bambergæ, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stehle, 143—5, Q. Disputatio Inaug. Juridica Judiciorum formam exhibens, &c. &c. &c. Auct. A. J. Stehle. Heidelbergae, 1731.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stengel, 124—4, Q. De Sequestro, &c. &c Auct. P. H. Stengel. Heidelbergæ, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sweling, 326, O. Clavis scientiarum, vulgo Logica, perfectioni suae restituta, per Johannem Eberhardum Sweling, J. U. D. &c. Bremæ, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theophilus, 76, Q. Theophili Antecessoris Institutionum libri IV. Carolus Annibal Fabrotus Antecessor Aquisextiensis ex tribus MSS. Codd. Biblioth. Regiae recensuit et Scholiis Graecis auxit. Idémque Jacobi Curtii Latinam interpretationem emendavit, et Notas adjecit. Græcè et Latinè. Parisiis, 1679.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Theoria, &c. 123—6, Q. Theoria Facultatis Repræsentandi, &c. &c. &c. &c. Bambergæ, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Thyllius 141—5, Q. C. O. Thyllii Spicilegiorum, &c. &c. Specimen quartum, &c. &c, etc. Subm. P. W. L. Flad.— Heidelbergæ. 1731.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Trautenberg. 139—2, Q. De Scientia, ejusque genuinis principiis cognoscendi verum, &c. &c, &c. Auct. D. Chr. P. L. B. de Trautenberg. Wirceburgi, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Trost, 141—6, Q. De Actionibus forensibus, &c. &c., Auct. J. F. Trost. Heidelbergi, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Turnbull 120. 0. The Principales of Moral Philosophy. An Enquiry into the wise and good Government of the World, &c. &c. By George Turnbull, LL. D. 2 vols. London, 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Van Espen, 48, F. Zegeri Bernardi Van Espen Juris utriusque Doctor, &c. Opera omnia. 2 tom. Coloniae Agrippinae, 1729.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Veri de Sensu, &c. 39—6, Q. De Sensu Veri, &c. &c. Wirceburgi, 1774.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Victor, 145—4, Q. De eo quod justum est circa Bonorum immobilium ad Manus Mortuas Translationes, &c. &c. Auct. A. E. Victor. Moguntiae, 1746.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vitriarius, 508, O. Phil. Reinh. Vitriarii Institutiones Juris Naturae et Gentium. Ad methodum Hugonis Grotii conscriptae et auctae a Joh. Jac. Vitriario. Accedit Joh. Franc. Buddei Historia Juris Naturalis, ut et Synopsis Juris Naturalis et Gentium juxta disciplinam Ebraeorum. Lugduni Batavorum, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vogt, 97. —2, Q. Specimen Gentium de Neutralitate, &c. Auct. J. A. Vogt. Bambergæ, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vogt,  143—3, Q. De Neutralitate, &c. Auct. J. A. Vogt.— Bambergæ, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wagner, 119—5, Q. De legislatoria Poenas Statuendi potestate, etc. Auct. C. Wagner. Wirceburgi, 1778.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Watts, 166, O. Logick: or the right Use of Treason in the Enquiry after Truth. With a Variety of Rules to guard against Error, in the Affairs of Religion and Human Life, as well as in the Sciences. By Isaac Watts, D. D. London, 1751.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Watts, 143 O. The same Work. London, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Weisserth, 91—5, Q. Ichnographia conclusionum ex universo Jure, etc. etc. Auctt. PP. EF. Ab. Weisserth, et Rog. Kayser. Bambergæ, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wurzfeld, 143—2, Q. De Jure et Jurisdictione Abbatum, etc. etc. etc. Auct. P. C. Würzfeld. Wirceburgi, 1736.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Acherley, 68, F. The Britannic Constitution: or, the Fundamental Form of Government in Britian. Demonstrating, the Original Contract entered into by the King and people, according to the Primary Institutions thereof, in this Nation, &c. &c &c. By Roger Acherley, Esq. With a Supplement, &c. London, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>American Philosophical Society, 33, O. Transactions of the Historical and Literary Committee of the American Philosophical Society, held at Philadelphia, &c. Vol. I.- Philadelphia, 1819.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Anquetil, 66, O. A Summary of Universal history; exhibiting the Rise, Decline, and Revolutions of the different Nations of the World, from the Creation to the present Time. Translated from the French of M. Anquetil, Member of the National Institute of France, &c. 9 vols. Philadelphia, 1806.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Anville, d&apos; 5, F. A Complete Body of Ancient Geography; by Mons. d&apos;Anville. 13 Plates; with the Modern Names of Places inserted under the ancient. London, 1806.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Arcq, d’ 34, Q. Histoire Generale des Guerres, depuis le Déluge jusqu’ a l’Année 1748. Avec une Dissertation sur chaque Peuple, &c. Par M. le Chevalier d’Arcq. 2 tom. A Paris, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>L&apos;Art de Verifier les Dates, &c. 40, F. L&apos;Art de verifier les Dates des Faits Historiques, des Chartes, des Chroniques, et autres Anciens Monumens, depuis la Naissance de Notre-Seigneur, etc. etc. Par un Religieux Benedictin de la Congregation de St. Maur. Tome premier. A Paris, 1783.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aurora, Editor of, 53—8, O. Charges against the Editor of the Aurora refuted.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bancks, 220, O. A Compendious History of the House of Austria and the German Empire, &c. &c. By John Bancks. London.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barbary, 217, O. A Compleat History of the Piratical States of Barbary, viz. Algiers, Tunis, Tripoli and Morocco, &c. &c. London, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barlow, 53—10, O. Barlow’s Letter to his fellow Citizens.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barnes, 64, F. The History of that most victorious Monarch Edward III. King of England and France, and Lord of Ireland, &c.; together with that of his most renowned Son Edward, Prince of Wales and Aquitain, sirnamed the Black Prince, &c. By Joshua Barnes, B. D., &c Portrait. Cambridge, 1688.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bayle, 46. F. A General Dictionary, Historical and Critical; in which a new and accurate Translation of that of the celebrated Mr. Bayle, with the Conrections and Observations printed in the late Edition at Paris is included, and interspersed with several thousand Lives never before published, &c. &c. With Reflections on such passages of Mr. Bayle. as seem to favour Scepticism and the Manichee System. By the Rev. John Peter Bernard; the Rev. Thomas Birch; John Lockman; and other hands; the Articles relating to oriental history, by George Sale, Gent. 10 vols. London, 1734—1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Benezet, 28, D. Some Account of Guinea, its Situation, &c.— With an Essay on the Slave Trade, &c. &c. By Anthony Benezet. Philadelphia, 1761.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Belleisle 124—1, F. Lettres de M. le Marêchal Duc de Belleisle, à M. le Marêchal de Contades, trouvées parmi les papiers de M. Contades après la Bataille de Minden.— 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Blair, 10, F. The Chronology and History of the World, from the Creation to the year of Christ, 1753, illustrated in LVI. &quot;Tables; of which IV. are.introductory and include the Centuries prior to the Ist Olympiad; and each of the remaining Lll. contain in one expanded View, 50 Years, or Half a  Century. By the Rev. John Blair, II. D. London, 1754,</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bodinus, 279, O. Joan. Bodini Andegavensis de Republica libri sex, Latine ab Auctore redditi, &c. Ursellis, 1601.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bolingbroke. 145, O. Letters on the Study and Use of history. By the Right Hon. Henry St. John, Lord Viscount Bolingbroke. London, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bolingbroke. 174, O. Remarkes on the History of England, (by Lord Bolingbroke.) London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>British America, 144, O. The British Empire in America, containing the tistory of the Discovery, Settlement, Progress, and State of the British Colonies in the continent and Island of America. 2 vols. London, 1741.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Burk, 100, O. The History of Virginia, commenced by John Burk, and continued by Skelton Jones, and Louis Hue Girardin. 4 vols. Petersburg. (Va.) 1804—1816.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Callender, 53—4, O. Letters to Alexander Hamilton, by Callen- der. New York, 1802.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Carte, 36, F. A General History of England. From the earliest Times to the year 1654. By Thomas Carte, an Englishman. 4 vols. London, 1747–1755.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catrou, 41, F. The Roman History; with Notes historical, geographical and critical; and lllustrated with Copperplates, Maps, and a great number of authentick Medals. Done into English, from the original French of the Rev. Fathers Catrou and Rouillé. With a summary of the Work. 6 vols. London, 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catrou,  8, Q. Aggregate Amount of each Description of Persons in the United States and their Territories, according to the Census, taken in virtue of the Acts of Congress of 1820 and 1821. With a List of the Taxable Inhabitants, &c. &c. in Pennsylvania in 1821; a Summary of of the Census of New York in 1821. Also Coxe’s Statement of the Arts and Manufactures of the United States. Philad. 1822. (Presented by R. De Silver.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Census of the United States, &c. 7, F. Census of the United States for 1820. Published by authority of an Act of Congress. Washington, 1821.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chamberlayne, 110, O. Magnae Britanniae Notitia: or, the Present State of Great Britain; with divers Remarks upon the Antient State thereof. By John Chamberlayne, Esq. London, 1723.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clairac, La Mamye- 18, D. Histoire de Perse, depuis le com mencement de ce Siecle. Par La Mamye-Clairac. 3 tom. A Paris, 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clarendon, 22, F. The History of the Rebellion and Civil Wars in England, begun in the year 1641. With the precedent Passages, and Actions, that contributed thereto, and the happy End and conclusion thereof by the King&apos;s blessed Restoration and Return, upon the 29th of May in the year 1660. Written by the Right Hon. Edward Earl of Clarendon. Portraits aud Plates. 3 vols. in 1. Oxford, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cluverus, 112, Q. Johannis Cluveri Historiarum totius Mundi Epitome a prima Rerum Origine usque ad annum Christi MDCXXX, ex sexcentis amplius Authoribus sacris profanisque, deducta, &c. Accessit per ipsum Authorem continuatio Historiae ad annum MCCXXXIII, nunc aucta ad annum MDCLIII. Lugduni Batavorum, 1657.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress of the United States, 25, 0. Secret Journals of the Acts and Proceedings of Congress, from the first meeting thereof, to the dissolution of the Confederation, by the adoption of the Constitution of the United States. 4 vols. Boston, 1821.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of, 24. O. Journals of Congress, containing their Proceedings from September 5, 1774, to November 3, 1788. 13 vols. Philadelphia, 1800—1801.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of,  26, O. Journals of the House of Representatives of the United States, commencing with the second session of Thirteenth Congress, and concluding with the 2d session of the Eighteenth Congress, both inclusive. 12 vols. —  Washington, 1813—1824.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of, 27, O. Journals of the Senate of the United States, commencing with the second session of the Thirteenth Congress, and concluding with the second session of the Eightteenth Congress, both inclusive. 12 vols. Washington, 1813—1824.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of, 12, O. State Papers, 2d Session, 13th Congress. 3 vols. Washington, 1813—1814.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of,  13, O. State Papers, 3d Session, 13th Congress. 3 vols. Washington, 1814.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of,  14, O. State Papers, 1st Session, 14th Congress. 3 vols. Washington, 1815—1816.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of, 15, O. State Papers, 2d Session, 14th Congress. 3 vols. Washington, 1816—1817.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of,  16, O. State Papers, 1st Session, 15th Congress. 10 vols. Washington, 1817—1818.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, Jounals of,  17, O. State Papers, 2d Session, 15th Congress. 10 vols. Washington, 1818—1819.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 18, O. State Papers, 1st Session, 16th Congress. 14 vols. Washington, 1819—1820.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 19, O. State Papers, 2d Session, 16th Congress. 15 vols. Washington, 1820—1821.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 20, O. State Papers, 1st Session, 17th Congress. 14 vols. Washington, 1821—1822.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress,  21, O. State Papers, 2d Session, 17th Congress. 14 vols. Washington, 1822—1823.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 22, O. State Papers, 1st Session, 18th Congress. 17 vols. Washington, 1823—1824.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 23, O. State Papers, 2d Session, 18th Congress. 15 vols. Washington, 1824—1825.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress,  88, F. State Papers, 2d Session, 13th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 89, F. State Papers, 2d Session, 13th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 90, F. State Papers, 3d Session, 13th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 91, F. State Papers, 1st Session, 14th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 92, V. State Papers, 1st Session, 14th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress,  93, F. State Papers, 1st Session, 14th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress,  94, F. State Papers, 2d Session, 14th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 95, F. State Papers, 2d Session, 14th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 96, F. State Papers, 2d Session, 14th Congress. Washington.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Congress, 52—2, O. Debate in the Senate of the United States on an Armendment of the Second article of the Constitution—reported 1804. Philadelphia,1804.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Coxe, 58, O. A View of the United States of America, in a Series of Papers, written at various times, between the  years of 1787 and 1794, by Tench Com, of Philadelphia; with Documents, &c. Philadelphia, 1794.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>D&apos;Avenant, 80, O. The Political and Commercial Works of that celebrated Writer Charles D’Avenant, LL. D. relating to the Trade and Revenue of England, the Plantation Trade, the East India Trade, and African trade. Collected and revised by Sir Charles Whatworth, M. P. 5 vols. London, 1771.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>De Colme, 142, O. The Constitution of England, or, an Account of the English Government; in which it is compared both with the Republican form of Government, and the other Monarchies of Europe. By J. L. De Lolme, Advocate, &c. Dublin, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Des Fontaines, 226, O. The history of the Revolutions of Poland, from the Fundation of that Monarchy to the Death of Augustus II. By M. l&apos;Abbé Des Fontaines. Translated from the French. London, 1736.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Desormeaux, 35, Q. Histoire de la Maison de Bourbon. Par M. Desormeaux, Historiographe de la Maison de Bourbon, &c. 3 tom. A Paris, 1772.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Diaz, del Castillo, 37, Q. The True History of the Conquest of Mexico, by Captain Bernal Diaz, del Castillo, one of the Conquerors. Written in 1568. Translated from the original Spanish by Maurice Keatinge, Esq. London, 1800.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dictionary, Biographical 153, O. A New and General Biographical Dictionary: containing an historical and critical Account of the Lives and Writings of the most eminent persons in every nation, particularly the British and Irish; from the earliest Accounts of Time to the present Period. With a Catalogue of their productions, &c. 2c. 11 vols. (Vol. IV. wanting. London, 1761—1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dwight, 51—4, O. Dwight&apos;s Letter to Washington. Philad. 1796.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Echard, 29, F. The History of England: from the first Entrance of Julius Caesar and the Romans, to the Conclusion of the Reign of King James the second, and the establishment of King William and Queen Mary upon the Throne, in the year 1688, &c. By Lawrence Echard, A. M. &c. Portrait. London, 1720.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>England, History of, 133, O. The History of England from the invasion of Julius Caesar to the year 1688. 11 vols (Vol. II. wanting.) Dublin, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>England, History of, 194, O. The Cristical History of England, Ecclesiastical and Civil: wherein the Errors of the Monkish Winters, and others before the Reformation, are exposed and corrected, &c. &c. 2 vols. London, 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>England, History of, 3, Q. England illustrate, or, a Compendium of the Natural Heiory, Geography, Topography, and Antiquities, ecclesiastical and civil, of England and Wales. With Maps and Engravings of many remains of Antiquity, remarkable Buildings, and principal Towns. 2 vols. London, 1764.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 72, D. Magni Des. Erasmi Roterodami Vita; partim ab ipsomet Erasmo, partim ab amicis aequalibus fideliter descripta. Accedunt Epistolae illustres plus quam Septuaginta, quas aetate provectiore scripsit nec inter vulgatas in magno volumine comparent. P. Scriverii, et Fautorum auspiciis. Lugduni Batavorum, 1642.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>France, history of, 230, O. The history of France from the Origin of that Nation to the beginning of the present Century. With an Account of the Steps taken by their late Princes to subvert their Civil Liberties, &c. &c. &c. Many Portraits. 2 vols. London, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Franklin, 94, 0. An Historical Review of the Constitution and Government of Pennsylvania, from its Origin; so far as regards the several Points of Controversy which have from Time to Time, arisen between the several Governors of that Province, and their several Assemblies.— Founded on authentic Documents. London, 1759.— (Presented by Dr. Franklin.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gale, 105, F. Historiæ Britannicæ, Saxonicæ, Anglo-Danicæ Schiptores XV. nempe, Gildas, Eddius, Ninnius, Asserius, Ran. Higden., W. Malmesh., Anonymus Malinesb., Anonymus Rames., Anonymus Elyens., Thomas Elyens., Joan. Wallingford, Rad. de Diceto, Anonymus, Joan. Ferdun., Alcwinus Flaccus, ex vetustis Codd. MSS. editi, opera Thomae Gale, Th. Pr. Oxoniae, 1691.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gallatin, 53—1, O. Views of the Public Debt and Expenditure, by Gallatin. Philadelphia, 1801.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Government, &c. 52—6, O. Experience the Test of Government, &c. by a Senator of Pennsylvania. Philadelphia, 1807.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Greene, 8, 0. Memoirs of the Life and Campaigns of  the Hon. Nathaniel Greene, Major General in the Army of the United States, &c. By Charles Caldwell, M. D., &c. Portrait. Philadelphia, 1819. (Presented by R. De Silver.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Guyon, de 182, O. The History of the East Indies, Ancient and Modern. Partly translated from the French of the Abbé de Guyon, &c. 2 vols. London, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hamilton, 52—7, O. A Letter from Alexander Hamilton, respecting the public conduct and character of John Adams, Esq. President, &c. Philadelphia, 1800.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Henry, 93, O. The History of Great Britain, from the first Invasion of it by the Romans under Julius Cæsar. Written on a New Plan. By Robert Henry, D. D. &c. Portrait. 12 vols. London, 1805.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heylyn 30, F. Cosmography, in four books. Containing the Chorography and History of the whole World: and all the Principal Kindoms, Provinces, Seas, and the Isles thereof. By Peter Heylyn, D. D. Improved with a Historical continuation to the present Times, by Edmund Bohun, Esq. Maps. London, 1703.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Historiæ Byzantinae Scriptores, &c. 12, F. Historiae Byzandinae Scriptores post Theophanem, partim nunc primum editi, partim recensiti, et nova Versione adornati. Cura et Studio R. P. Francisci Combefisii. Græce et Latine. Parisiis, 1785.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>History, Universal, 139, O. An Universal history, from the Earliest Account of Time. Compiled from original Author;  and illustrated with Maps, Cuts. Notes, &c. The Ancient part in 20 vols., the Modern in 40 vols. (Vols 31, 38, 39, wanting.) London, 1747—1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hooke, 127, O. The Roman history, from the building of Rome to the Ruin of the Commonwealth. By N. Hooke, Esq. 4 vols. Dublin, 1759.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Howel, 52, F. An Institution of General History, or, the History of the World. Being a complete Body thereof from the beginning of the World till the Monarchy of Constantine the Great, dc. &c.&c. By William Howel, LL. D. &c. 3 vols. London, 1680.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Huberus 104, Q. Ulrici Huberi Institutiones Historiae Civilis, quae continent summam rerum toto Orbe Gestarum ab ortu Imperiorum, usque ad medium saeculum à Christi nato decimum septimum. Cura Zach. Huberi, Ulr. Fil. Franequeræ. 1703.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hulchinson, 65, O. The history of Massachusetts, from the first settlement thereof in 1628, until the year 1750. By Thomas Hutchinson, Esq. &c. 2 vols. Boston, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ingersoll, 32, O. A View of the Right and Wrongs, Power and Policy, of the United States of America. By Charles Jared Ingersoll. Philadelphia, 1808.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jaligny, 45, F. Histoire de Charles VIII. Roy de France, par Guillaume de Jaligny, André de La Vigne, et autres Historiens de ce temps-là. Où sont decrites les Choses les plus memorables arrivées pendant ce Regne depuis 1483 jusques en 1498. Enrichi de plusieurs Memoires, Observations, &c. &c. &c. Le tout recueilli par feu M. Godefroy, Historiographe, &c. A Paris, 1684.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Joinville. 26, F. Histoire de Saint Louis, par Jehan, Sire de Joinville.—Les Annales de son Regne, par Guillaume de Nangis.—Sa Vie et ses Miracles, par le Confesseur da la Reine Marguerite.—Le tout publié d&apos;après les MSS. de la Bibliotheque du Roi, et accompagné d&apos;un Glossaire. A Paris, 1761.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Journals, &c. 23, F. Journals of the House of Representatives of the Commonwealth of Pennsilvania. Beginning Nov. 28th. 1776, and ending Oct. 2d. 1781. With the Proceedings of the several Committee and Conventions, before and at the commencement of the American Revolution. Vol. I. Philadelphia, 1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Journals, 112, 0. Journals of the House of ‘Representatives of the Commonwealth of Pennsilvania, from Dec. 6, 1803, to April 1, 1823, (14th. to 33d. House inclusive.) 21 vols. Lancaster and Harrisburg, 1803–1823.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Journals, 113, 0. Journals of the Senate of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, from Dec. 4, 1804, to April 1, 1823. (vols. XV. to XXXIII. inclusive.) 21 vols. Lancaster and Harrisburg, 1804—1823. Journals,  of the House of Representatives of the United States,</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kæmpfer, 85, F. The History of Japan; giving an Account of the Antient and present State and Government of that Empire, of its Temples, Castles, &c.; of its Metals, Minerals, Trees, Plants, Animals, &c.&c. Together with a Description of the Kingdom of Siam. Written in High Dutch by Engelbertus Käempfer, M. D. &c. and translated from his Original Ms. by J. G. Scheuchzer, F. R. S., &c. With the Life of the Author and an Introduction. Also, Part of a Journal of a Voyage to Japan, made by the English in 1673. Illustrated with many copperplates. 2 vols. London, 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Kennet, 31, F, A complete History of England: with the Lives of all the Kings and Queens thereof; from the Earliest Account of Time, to the Death of his late Majesty King William III. Containing a faithful Relation of all Af- fairs of State, Ecclesiastical and Civil, &c. Lc. By Milton, Daniel, Habington, Moore, Buck, LordBacon, Lord Herbert, Haywood, Francis, Bishop of Hereford, Cambden, Wilson, and Kennet. With notes, &c.- 3 vols. London, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Laet, de, 102, F. Novis Orbus, seu Descriptiones Indiae Occidentalis Libri XVIII. Authori Joanne de Laet, Antverp. Novis Tabulis Geographicis et variis Animantium, Plantarum, Fructuumque Iconibus illustrati. Lugduni Batavorum, apud Elzevirios, 1633.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Linda, de, 283, O. Lucae de Linda Descriptio Orbis et omnium ejus Rerumpublicarum. Lugduni Batavorum, 1655.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Livius, 126, O. The Roman History, by Titus Livius; with the entire Supplement of John Freinsheim; translated into English, and illustrated with geographical and chronological notes. Vols. II, III, IV, V, VI. London, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lonicerus. 309, O. Historia Turcica, in qua Turcorum Origo, Principes, Imperatores, Bella, &c. &c. exponuntur. Accessere, Narratio de Baiazethis filiorum seditionibus; Turcicarum rerum epitome, quomodo captivi Christiani distrahantur, &c. &c. &c. Omnia collecta, Sermoneque Latina exposita, a D. Philippo Lonicero. Tom. 2 in 1. Francofurti, 1584.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Louisiana, 53—9, O. An Account of Louisiana. Philad. 1803.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ludlow, 116, F. Memoirs of Edmund Ludlow, Esq. Lieut. Gen. of Horse, Commander in Chief of the Forces in Ireland, Member of the Parliament which begun on November 3, 1640,&c. With a collection of original Papers, serving to confirm and illustrate many important Passages contained in the Memoirs. Also, the Case of King Charles the First. London, 1751.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Macaulay 14, Q. The History of England from the Accession of James I. to that of the Brunswick Line. By Catharine Macaulay. 2 vols. London, 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Macaulay  118, O. The History of England from the Accession of James I. to the Election of the House of Hanover. By Catharine Macaulay. Vols. II, III, IV. London, 1769</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Major, 63, Q. Historia Majoris Britanniae, tam Angliae quam Scotiae, per Joannem Majorem, nomine quidem Scotum, professione autem Theologum, è veterum monumentis concinnata. Edinburgi, 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Memorial, in answer to English Ministers, &c. 293, O. A Memorial containing a Summary View of Facts, with their Authorities, in Answer to the Observations sent by the English Ministry to the Courts of Europe. Translated from the French. Philadelphia, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Messenger, America Weekly, 2, O. The American Weekly Messenger; or Register of State Papers, History, and Politics. For 1813-14-15 and 16. 2 vols. Philadephia. (Presented by R. De Silver.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mississippi question, 51—9, 0. Mississippi Question. Report of a Debate in the Senate of the United States, February, 1803. Philadelphia, 1803.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Monroe, 40, O. A View of the Conduct of the Executive, in the Foreign Affairs of the United States, connected with the Mission to the French Republic, during the year 1794, &apos;95, and &apos;96. By James Monroe, late Minister, &c. — With documents, &c. Philadelphia, 1797.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Newton, 99—2, Q. Sir Isaac Newton&apos;s Chronology, abridged by himself.-Some Observations on ditto; printed at Paris in 1725. Done into English.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>New York Historical Society, 6, O. Collections of the New York Historial Society for the year 1821. Vol. III. New York, 1821.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nexu, de &c, 97—3, Q. De Nexu Historiae cum Scientiis, &c. Wirceburgi, 1774.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nicephorus, 14, F. Nicephori Gregorae Byzantina Historia. Cum versione latina Hier. Wolfii, et Joh. Boivin. qui Codices contulit, Notas addidit, et alias Appendices. Graece et Latine. Tom 2. Parisiis, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Noldius, 63, D. Christ. Noldii Historia Idumaea, seu, de Vita et gestis Herodum Diatribe. Accesserunt hinc inde Notae in Josephum: ut et pro eo vindiciae et responsiones, contra Baronium, Serarium, Salianum et alios. Franequerae, 1660.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Paine, 51—10, O. Paine on Government. Paris, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Paine, 51—6, O. Speech of T. Paine, July 7, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Paine, 51—2, O. Letter to Washington. By Paine. Philadelphia, 1796.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Paine,  52—4, O. Speech in the French Convention, by Paine.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Paine,  52—3, O. The Decline and Fall of the English Finance, by Paine.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Paine,  53—5, O. Paine on Government. Paris, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Parker, 101, O. Memoirs of the most remarkable Military Transactions from the year 1683, to 1718. Containing a particular account of the several Battles, Sieges, &c. in Ireland and Flanders, during the Reigns of King William and Queen Anne. By Capt. Robert Parker, late of the Royal Regiment of Foot in Ireland, who was an Eye-witness to most of them. London, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Patterson, 53—7, O. Petition of Alexander Paterson to the Legislature of Pennsylvania. Lancaster, 1804.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Perizonius, 324, O. Jac. Perisonii Rerum per Europam maxime Gestarum ab ineunte Saeculo sextodecimo usque ad Caroli V. Mortem, &c. Commentarii Historici. Lugduni Batavorum, 1716.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Petavius, 336, O. D. Petavii Aurelianensis e Soc. Jesu, Rationarium Temporum, in quo aetatum omnium sacra profanaque historia Chronologicis probationibus munita summatim traditur. Franequeræ, 1694.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pickering 51—8, O. Pickering&apos;s Three Letters. Philad. 1799</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Puffendorf, 221, O. An Introduction to the History of the principal Kingdoms and States of Europe. Begun by Baron Puffendorf. Enlarged, &c.; continued down to the year 1743, by M. Martiniere. Improved from the French by Joseph Sayer. 2 vols. London, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rawlinson, 219, O. A New Method of Studying History, &c.; with a Dissertation of Count Maffei on the use of Inscriptions and Medals, &c. By Richard Rawlinson, LL. D. &c. 2 vols. London, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Register, Annual, 28, O. The Annual Register, (Dodsley’s) or, a View of the History, Politics, and Literature, for the years 1758 to 1794, inclusive. 37 vols. (vols. 11. 17. 23. 25. 27, 28, 29. 33, 34, wanting.) London, 1768—1799.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>New Annual, 29, O. The New Annual Register, or, general Repository of History, Politics, and Literature, for the years 1795 to 1801, inclusive. 7 vols. Lond. 1796—1802.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>American, 39, O. The America Register, or General Repository of History, Politics, and science, for 1810. Vol. VII. Philadelphia, 1811.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Robertson, 117, O. The History of Scotland during the Reigns of Queen Mary and of King James VI. till his accession to the Crown of England. With a Review of the Scottish history previous to that Period. An Appendix, &c. &c. By William Robertson, D. D. &c. 2 vols. London, 1761. (Presented by David Hall.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rollin, 13, D. The Ancient History of the Egyptians, Carthaginians, Assyrians, Babylonians, Medes and Persians, Macedonians and Grecians. By Mr. Rollin. 10 vols. (vols. 1, 2, and 7 wanting.) Edinburg, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rollin, 187, O. The Roman History from the Fundation of Rome to the Battle of Actium; that is, to the End of the Commonwealth. By Mr. Rollin. Translated from the French. Mapls and plates. 16 vols. (Vol. I. wanting.) London, 1754.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sampson, &c. 51—7, O. Sampson against the Philistines,, &c.— Philadelphia, 1805.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Savage, 190, O. A compleat History of Germany, comprehending the Lives and Reigns of all the Emperors from its origin to this Time. By Mr. Savage. With many Portraits. London, 1702.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Scaligerus, 62, F. Josephi Sealigeri JulI Caesaris F. Opus de Emendatione Temporum. Addita veterum Graecorum Fragmenta selecta, &c. Cum Notis ejusdem Scaligeri. Coloniae Allobrogum, 1629.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Selden, 7, Q. An historical and Political Discourse of the Laws and Government of England, from the First times to the End of the Reign of Queen Elizabeth. With a Vindication of the Antient Way of Parliament, in England. Collected from some Manuscript Notes of John Selden, Esq. by Nathaniel Bacon, Esq. Corrected and improved by a Gentleman of the Middle Temple. London, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Seybert, 6, Q. Statistica. Annals; embracing Views of the Population, Commerce, Navigation, Fisheries. Public Lands, Post Office Establishment, Revenues, Mint, Military and Naval Establishments, Expenditures, Public Debt, and Sùnking Fund of the United States of America: founded on Official Documents: commencing March 4, 1789, and ending April 20, 1818. By Adam Seybert, M. D, &c. Philadelphia, 1818.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sidney, 198, O. Discourses concerning Government; by Algernon Sidney, &c. With his Life. 2 vols. Edinb. 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Smith, 135, O. The History of the Province of New York from the first Discovery to the year 1732. With a Description of the Country, &c. &c. &c. By William Smith, A. M. Philadelphia, 1792.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Smollet, 67, O. A complete History of England, from the Descent of Julius Cæsar, to theucaty of Aix la Chapelle, 1748. Containing the Transactions of one thousand eight hundred and three years. By F. Smollet, M. D. 7 vols. (Vol. I. wanting.) London, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Steele, 99—4, Q. The Crisis: or, a Discourse representing, from the most authentic Records, the just Causes of the late  happy Revolution, &c. &c. With some Remarks on the Danger of a Popish Succession. By Richard Steele, Esq. London, 1714.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Steele, 99—3, Q. Mr. Steele&apos;s Apology for himself and his witings; occasioned by his Expulsion from the House of Commons. London, 1714.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Strada, 49, D. Famiani Stradæ, Romani, e Soc. Jesu, de Bello Belgico, Decades duae, ab Excessu Caroli V. Imp. usque ad annum MDXC. Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1648—1650.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sully, 92, O. Memoirs of Maximilian de Bethune, Duke de Sully, prince Minister to Henry the Great. Containing the history of the Life and Reign of that Monarch, and his own Administration under him. With the Tryal of Ravaillac for the murder of Henry the Great. Translated from the French. 5 vols. London, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tacitus, 21, D. Tibère, ou les six premiers livres des Annales de Tacite. Traduits par M. l&apos;Abbé de la Bléterie, Prof. &c. 3 tom. A Paris, 1768.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Terasson 229, 0. The Life of Sethos. Taken from private Memoirs of the Ancient Egyptians. Translated from a Greek MSS. into French (by the Abbe Terasson,) and from the French by Mr. Lediard. 2 vols. Lond. 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Treatys, Declarations, &c. 272, O. A General collection of Treatys, Declarations of War, Manifestoes, and other public Papers, relating to Peace and War, among the Potentates of Europe, from 1648 to the present Time, &c. &c. &c. London, 1710.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Varenius, 254, O. A Compleat System of General Geography, &c. &c. etc. Originally written in Latin by Bernhard Varenius, M. D. improved, &c. by Sir Isaac Newton, and Dr. Jurin. Translate, &c. by Mr. Dugufale, revised &c. by Peter Slaw, M. D. Vol. I. Plates. Lond. 1734.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vertot, 4, D. Histoire des Revolutions de Suede, por M. l&apos;Abbé de Vertot. 2 tom. in 1. A Amsterdam, 1722.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vertot, 224, O. The history of the Revolutions in Sweden and Portugal. With an Enquiry, whether the Kingdom of France, from the Establishment of that Monarchy, has been an Hereditary or Elective State. Translated from the French of the Abbé Vertot. Dublin, 1727.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vertot, 146, O. The History of the Revolutions that happened in the Government of the Roman Republic. Translated from the French of the Abbé de Vertot, by M. Ozell. With Earl Stanhope’s Memorial on the Roman Senate, &c. &c. to the Abbé de Vertot, and his answer. 2 vols. London, 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vertot, 57, Q. Observations on, I. The answer of M. l’ Abbé de Vertot to Earl Stanhope’s Inquiry concerning the Senate of ancient Rome; dated Dec. 1719.—II. A Dissertation upon the Constitution of the Roman Senate: by a Gentleman: published in 1743. III. A Treatise on the Roman Senate by Dr. Middleton; published in 1747. IV. An Essay on the Roman Senate, by Dr. Chapman; published in 1750. By Mr. Hooke. London, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Voltaire, 10, D. The Age of Lewis XIV. Translate from the French of M. de Voltaire. 2 vols, Dublin, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>War in the Netherlands, &c. 160, O. The Theatre of the present War in the Netherlands, and upon the Rhine, &c. With an Introduction to the Art of Fortification, or Military Dictionary, &c. Map, and 68 plans of Fortified places. London, 1745. (Presented by Lewis Evans.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Washington, 37, O. The Life of George Washington, &c. By David Ramsey, M. D. New York, 1807.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Washington,  51—5, O. Letters from Washington to his friends in June and July, 1776. Philadelphia, 1795.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Washington, 51—3, O. Remarks on the Conduct of Washington. — Philadelphia, 1797.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Wilkinson 2, F. A General Atlas, consisting of the World and Quarters, Kindoms, States, and with all the New Discoveries and Territorial Arrangements, &c. &c. 62 Maps. Published by Wilkinson. London, 1802.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Zonaras, 13, F. Joannis Zonarae Monarchi antea vigilum Praefecti et primi a Secretis Annales. Carolus du Fresne, Dom. du Cange, Wolfianum Editionem cum scriptis Codd. contulit: Latinam Versionem recensuit, Annales Notis illustravit. Graece et Latine. Tom. 2. Parisiis, 1686.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Zosimus 299, O. Zosimi Comitis ex Advocati Fisci Historia nova, ex recensione, Frid. Sylburgii, cum Latina Interpretatione Joan. Leunclavii, et Notis Variorum, accurante Chr. Cellario. Græce et Latine. Jenæ, 1729.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>American Medical and Philosophical Register, 36, O. The American Medical and Philosophical Register: or Annals of Medicine, Natural History, Agriculture, and the Arts. 2 vols. New York, 1811—1812. (Presented by Dr. Hosack.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Banton, 74, O. A Treatise containing a Plan for the internal Organization and Government of Marine Hospitals in the United States: together with a scheme for amending and systematizing the MedicaI Department of the Navy. By W. P. C. Barton, M. D. &c. Philadelphia, 1814.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bell, 81 O. A System of Surgery, by Benjamin Bell. Vol. I. Edinburg, 1783.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bellinus, 108, Q. Laurentii Bellini Opuscula aliquot; in quibus praecipue agitur, de Motu Cordis in et extra Uterum, ovo, ovi aere et respiratione. De Motu Bilis et Liquidorum omnium per corpora animalium. De Fermentis et Glandulis, &c. Cum figuris. Lugduni Batavorum, 1714.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boerhave, 180, O. Dr. Boerhaave’s Academical Lectures on the Theory of Physic. Being a genuine Translation of his Institates and etcplanatory Comment, Lc. &c. 6 vols. (Vol. I. wanting.) London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boerhave,  206, O. Boerhaave’s Medical Correspondence; containing the various Symptoms of Chronical Distemper: the Professor’s opinion, method of Cure, and Remedies.— With his Practice in the Hospital at Leyden, &c. &c. London, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boerhave,  277, O. A Method of Studying Physick. Written in Latin by Hermann Boerhaave, translated into English by Mr. Samber. London, 1719.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Burnet, 131, Q. Thesaurus Medicinae Practicae, ex praestant. tum vet. tum recent. Medicorum Observationibus, Consultationibus, Consiliis et Epistolis collectus, &c &c. Studio et Opera Thomae Burnet, Scoto Britanni, M. D., &c. Londini, 1673.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Celsus, 71, O. A. Cornelius Celsus of Medicine, in eight books. Translated, with Notes Cristical and explanatory, by James Greive, M. D. London, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cheselden, 8, F. Osteographia, or the Anatomy of the Bones. fifty-six Plates. By William Cheselden. London.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cleghorn 148, O. Observations on the Epidemical Diseases in Minorca, from 1744 to 1749. With an Account of the Climate, Productions, &c. &c. &c. of the Island. By George Cleghorn, Lecturer of Anatomy, &c. &c. London, 1762. (Presented by David Wilson.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Corvisart, 72, O. An Essay on the Organic Diseases and Lesions of the Heart and Great Vessels. From the Clinical Lectures of J. N. Corvisart. Translated from the French, with Note, by Jacob Gates, M. M. S. S. — Philadelphia, 1812.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Coxe, 61 O. The American Dispensatory, containing the Natural, Chemical, &c. History of the different Substances employed in Medicine, the Operations of Pharmacy, &c. &c. By John Redman Coxe, M. D. &c. Phila- delphia, 1825. [Presented by the Editor.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Coxe, 62, O. The same Work. Philad. 1806.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Coxe, 35, O. The Philadelphia Medical Museum, conducted by John Redman Coxe, M. D. 6 vols. Plates. Philadelphia, 1805—1809. [Presented by the Editor.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Crawford, 140—5, O. Introductory Lectures, &c. by J. Crawford, M. D. Baltimore, 1811.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dimerbroeck, 127, Q. Isbrandi de Diemerbroeck Med. Doct. et Prof. Tractatus de Peste, truculentissimi Morbi Historiam ratione et experientiâ confirmatam exhibens. Amstelodami, 1665.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dorsey, 140—4, O. Syllabus, or Heads of Lectures on the Materia Medica, by J. S. Dorsey, M. D. Philad. 1817.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Fernelius, 287, O. Joannis Fernelii Universa Medicina. Lugduni Batavorum, 1645.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Fernelius,  291, O. Joannis Fernelii Universa Medicina. Cum ejusdem Fernelii Consiliis: et Guliel. Plantii Scholiis in Pharmacopoeam seu librum Therapeutices Septimum. Genevae, 1627.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Fernelius, 307, O. Joannis Fernelii de Morbis Universalibus et particularibus libri IV. posteriores Pathologiae. Adjecta est singulis morbis Praedicendi, Curandique Ratio. Lugdum Batavorum, 1645.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gibson, 11. O. The Institutes and Practice of Surgery: being the Outlines of a Course of Lectures, by William Gibson, M. D. Plates. Vol. I. Philad. 1824. [Presented by the Author.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gregory, 73, O. A Dissertation on the Influence of a Change of Climate in curing Diseases, by Professor Gregory, of Edindurgh. Translated from the Latin, with Notes, by W. P. C. Barton, M. D. Philad. 1815.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hafenrefferus, 331. O. Officina Jatrica, continens Pharmaca selecta Hippocratico-Galenica, et Hermetica Paracelsica, juxta Morborum Seriem, causarumque Indicem disposita et condita per Samuelem Hafenrefferum, Phil. et Med. Prof. &c. Ulmae, 1653.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Haller, 140—10, O. Pathological Observations, chiefly from Dissections of Morbid Bodies. By Dr. Albert Haller.— London, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hare, 10, 0. A Viev of the Structure, Functions, and Disorders of the Stomach and Alimentary Organs of the Human Body, with Physiological Observations and Remarks upon the qualities and effects of Food and Fermented Liquors; by Thomas Hare, F. L. S. &c. Plates. London, 1821. [Presented by the Author.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hippocrates, 361, O. Aphorismi Hippocratis, Graece et Latine; juxta optimam editionem Theodori Janssoni ab Almeloveen, M. D. Anno 1685. Edinburgi, 1736.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Holland, 140—1, O. An Inaugural Dissertation on Apoplexy, by N. L. Holland. A. B. Philadelphia, 1815.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Jenty, 249, O. A Course of Anatomico-Physiological Lectures on the Human Structure and Animal Œconomy; with Notes, &c. & c. &.c. and Essays on Injecting, Dissecting, &c. 3 vols. By Charles Nicholas Jenty, M. A. [Vol I. wanting.] London, 1757.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lettsom, 18, Q. The Natural History of the Tea Tree, with Observations on the Medical Qualities of Tea, and on the Effects of Tea-drinking. By John Coakley Lettsom, M. D. Coloured Plates. London, 1799.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Morgan, 203, 0. De Puopoiesi, sive Teutamen Medicum Inaugarale de Puris Confectione. Auctore Johanne Morgan, A. M. &c. Edinburgi. 1763.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Morgan, 264, O. A Discourse upon the Institution of Medical Schools in America, delivered at a Commencement May 30, and 31, 1765. With a Preface, &c. &c. &c. By John Morgan, M. D., F. R. S. &c. Philadelphia, 1765.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Price, 140 —7, O. Inaugural Dissertation on the Magnolia Glauca, &c. &c. By T. D. Prince. Philadelphia, 1802.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Quesnay, 140—8, O. The Introductory Discourse to the first volume of the Memoirs of the Royal Academy of Surgery, at Paris, concerning the Vices of the Humours, &c. &c. By M. Quesnay, M. D. Translated and abridged, by a Surgeon. London, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Riverius, 61, F. Lazari Riverii Consil. Reg. Med. Prof. in Universitate Monspeliensi, &c. Opera Medica Omnia. Curâ Joh. Dan. Horstii et Joh. Jac. Doebelii. Lugduni, 1679.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Robertson, 140—9, O. Inaugural Dissertation on Chorea Sancti Viti. By F. Robertson. Philadelphia, 1805.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Stokes, 140—3, O. Dissertatio inauguralis de Asphyxia, &c.— Auct. G. Stokes, A, B. Philadelphia, 1793.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Tilton. 140—2, O. Dissertatio medica inauguralis. Auct. J. Tilton, M. B. Philadelphia, 1771.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Van Swieten, 154, O. The Commentaries upon the Aphorisms of Dr. Herman Boerhaave, concerning the Knowledge and Cure of the several Diseases incident to human Bodies. By Gerard Van Swieten, M. D. Translated into English. 11 vols. London, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Van Swieten,  5, D. The same Work. 18 vols. Edinburgh, 1776.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Verheyen, 107, Q. Supplementum Anatomicum, sive Anatomiae Corporis humani liber Secundus, &c.&c. &c. Authore Philippo Verheyen. Cum figuris. Bruxellis, 1710.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Winslow, 64, Q. Exposition Anatomique de la structure du Corps humain, par Jacques-Benigne Winslow, de l&apos;Academie Royale des Sciences, &c. Avec figures. A Paris, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Ali Ben Ali Taleb. 215, O. Ali Ben Abi Taleb Carmina. Arabice et Latine. Edidit et Notis illustravit Gerardus Kuypers, Franę. Fil. Lugduni Batavorum, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barlœus, 64, D. Casparis Barlaei Antverpiani Poemata. Tom. 2. Amstelodami, 1645</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barlœus, 354, O. The same Work. Lugduni Batavorum, 1628.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boileau, 40, D. Œuvres diverses du Sieur D. (Boileau) Avec le Traité du Sublime ou du Merveilleux dans le Discours, traduit du Grec de Longin. A Amsterdam, 1689.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Brancatus, 123—1, Q. Fr. Laurentii Brancati de Lauraea, S. R. E. Card. Theantropus Reparatus, Tragoedia, &c. &c. Wirceburgi, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Buchananus, 78, D. G. Buchanani Scoti Opera Poetica; cum ejusdem Vita ab ipso scripta biennio ante mortem.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Butler, 19, D. Hudibras, poëme de Samuel Butler, écrit pendant les Guerres Civiles d&apos;Angleterre, et traduit en Vers Français par J. Towneley, Officier Anglais au Service de France, avec des Remarques de Larcher, et quinze figures d&apos;apres Hogarth. Français et Anglois. 3 tom. A Paris, 1819.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cowley, 126, F. The Works of Mr. Abraham Cowley. Portrait. London, 1680.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 68, D. Desiderii Erasmi Roterodami Colloquia. Lugduni Batavorum, apud Elzevirium, 1643.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 35, D. Erasmi Colloquia selecta; with an English translation; by John Clarke. Philadelphia, 1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Knox, 63, O. Essays, Moral and Literary. By Vicesimus Knox, M. D. &c. 3 vols. London, 1787.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Metastasio, 54, O. Opere del Signor Abate Pietro Metastasio. In Parigi, 1780.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Milton, 122, F. Paradise Last. A Poem. By John Milton. With Explanatory Notes, &c. Portrait and Plates.— London, 1695.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Montaigne, 306, O. Les Essais de Michel Seigneur de Montaigne. Avec Annotations en Marge, &c. et la Vie de l&apos;Auteur extraicte de ses propres escrits. A Rome, 1627.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Spectator, 30, D. The Spectator. 8 vols. (Vols. V. and VI. wanting.) London, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Voiture, 48, D. Recueil des Œuvres de M. de Voiture. A Brusselles, 1695.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Williston, 49, O. Eloquence of the United States: compiled by E. B. Williston. 5 vols. Middletown, Conn. 1827.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Adam’s, 7, O. Report upon the Weights and Measures, by John Quincy Adams, Secretary of State of the United States. Prepared in obedience to a Resolution of the Senate of March 3d. 1817. Philadelphia, 1821.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>American Philosophical Society, 12, Q. Transactions of the American Philosophical Society, held at Philadelphia for promoting Useful knowledge. Vol. I. New series.— Philadelphia, 1818.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Aringhi, 54, D. Roma Subterranea novissima, in qua antiqua Christianorum et praecipue Martyrum Caemeteria, Tituli, &c. &c. illustrantur. Ex absolutissimo opere Pauli Aringhi, &c. Cum figuris. Arnhemiae, 1671.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Arts, Landmaid to the, 147, O. The Handmaid to the Arts. 2 vols. London, 1758. [Presented by David Hall.]</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Asiatic Researches, &c. 95, O. Asiatic Researches: or, Transactions of the Society intituted in Bengal for inquiring into the History and Antiquities of the Arts, Princes, and Literature, of Asia. Plates. 5 vols. London, 1798- 1799.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bacon, 60, O. The Works of Francis Bacon, Baron of Verulam, Viscount St. Alban, and Lord High Chancellor of England. Portrait, &c. 10 vols. London, 1819.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bacon, 58, D. Fr. Baconis de Verulam, Angliae Cancellarii, de Augmentis Scientiarum Libri IX. Amstelodami, 1662.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bailly, 236, O. Lettres sur l’Origine des Sciences, et sur celle des Peuples de l&apos;Asie, adressées à M. de Voltaire par M. Bailly, et precedées de quelques Lettres de M. de Voltaire à l&apos;Auteur. 2 tom. A Paris, 1777.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Banier, 168, O. The Mythology and Fables of the Ancients ex¬plained from History. By the Abbé Banier. Translated from the original French. Vols. II, III, and IV. London, 1740.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Barton, 24, Q. Florae Philadelphicæ Prodromus: or Prodromus of the Flora Philadelphica; exhibiting a List of all the Plants to be described in that Work, which have as yet been collected. By William P. C. Barton, M. D. &c. Philadelphia, 1815.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Birch, 23, Q. The History of the Royal Society of London for improving of Natural Knowledge, from its first Rise. In which the most considerable of those Papers communicated to the Society, which have hitherto not been  published, are inserted in their proper order, as a Supplement to the Philosophical Transactions. By Thomas Birch, D. D. Secretary to the Royal Society. Plates. 4 vols. London, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bougainville, 53, Q. Voyage autour du Monde, par la fregate du Roi la Boudeuse, et la flûte l&apos;Etoile en 1766, 1767, 1768 et 1769. Par M. de Bouganville. Avec des Cartes, &c. A Paris, 1771.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bourrit, 235, O. Description des Alpes Pennines et Rhetiennes; par M. T. Bourrit. Tom. II. A Geneve, 1781.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Boyle, 56, F. The Works of the Honourable Robert Boyle. To which is prefixed, the Life of the Author. Portrait. 5 vols. London, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Bradley, 157, O. A Dictionary of Plants; their Description and Use, with their Culture and Management. By R. Bradley, F. R. S. &c. 2 vols. London, 1747.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Buchananus, 68, Q. Georgii Buchanani, Scoti, Poëtarum sui Seculi facile Principis, Praeceptoris Jacobi VI. Scottorum et Primi Angl. Reg. Opera Omnia, Historica, Chronologica, Juridica, Politica, Satyrica and Poetica. Cum Notis, aliisque utilissimis Accessionibus illustrata et aucta, &c. &c. curante Thoma Ruddimanno, A. M. et Praefatione Petri Burmanni. Cum effigie. Tom. 2. Lugduni Batavorum, 1725.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Buffon, 42, Q. Histoire naturelle des Oiseaux. Par M. le Comte de Buffon. Avec plusieurs figures. 8 tom. A Paris, 1770—1781.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Buffon, 43, Q. Histoire Naturelle des Mineraux. Par M. le Comte de Buffon. Tom. I. A Paris, 1783.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Buffon, 41. Q. Histoire Naturelle, Générale et Particuliere, avec la Description du Cabinet du Roy. Par MM. Buffon et Daubenton. Avec plusieurs figures. 15 tom. (le tome XII. manque.)—Supplement a l&apos;Histoire Naturelle, Générale et Particuliere. Par M. le Comte de Buffon. Avec plusieurs figures. 6 tom. A Paris, 1749—1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Caldwell 140—6, O. Eulogium on Caspar Wistar, M. D. &c. by Charles Caldwell, M. D. &c. Philadelphia, 1818.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Callimaque, 238, 0. Hymnes de Callimaque avec une Verdion Françoise et des Notes. Par La Porte du Theil. Grec et François. A Paris, 1775.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catalogue of Books, &c. 9, 0. Catalogue of Books belonging to the Library Company of Philadelphia; with an Account of the Institution, &c. &c., &c. Philadelphia, 1807.— (Presented by the Library Company.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catalogue of Books, &c. 76—2, O. Catalogus Collegii Yalensis, 1808.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Catalogue of Books, &c.  106, O. Catalogus Bibliothecae Harvardianae Cantabrigiae Nov-Anglorum. Bostoniae, 1790.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Chamber, 20, F. Cyclopœdia: or, an Universal Dictionary of Arts and &ciences, c. &c. &e. By E. Chambers, F. R. S. Plates. 2 vols. London, 1751.—Supplement to ditto, 2 vols. London, 1753.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clothing French Prisoners, &c. 118. F. Proceedings of the Committee appointed to manage the Contributions begun at London, Dec. 18, 1759, for clothing French Prisoners of War. London, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Clothing French Prisoners, &c. 124—2, F. The same Work. London, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cooper. 57, O. A Practical Treatise on Dyeing, and Calicoe printing; exhibiting the processes in the French, German, English and American practice of fixing Colours on Woollen, Cotton, Silk, and Linen. By Thomas Cooper, Esq. Philadelphia, 1815.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cooper.  4, O. Some Information concerning Gas Lights, by Thomas Cooper, Esq. Philad. 1816. (Presented by R. De Silver.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Cooper.  59, O. The Emporium of Arts and Princes. New Series. Conducted by Thomas Cooper, Esq. Vols. II. and III. Plates. Philadelphia, 1813—1814.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Dalrymple, 122, O. A Military Essay. Containing Reflections on the Raising, Arming, Cloathing, and Discipline of the British Infantry and Cavalry: with Proposals for the Improvement of the same By Campbell Dalrymple, Esq. Lieut. Col. &c. London, 1761.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Delius, 45, Q. Traité sur la science de l’Exploitation des Mes par Théorie et Pratique, avec un Discours sur les principes des finances; fait pour l’Academie Impériale et Royale de Schemnitz, par Christothe François Delius, Conseil ler-Commissaire, &c. Traduit en Français par M. Schreiber. Avec figures. 2 tom. A Paris, 1778.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Education, Dialogues concerning, 87, O. Dialogues concerning Education. Vol. II. London. 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Encyclopædia, &c 13, Q. Encyclopaedia; or, a Dictionary of Arts, Sciences, and Miscellaneous Literature, &c. &c. &c. &c. With 542 Plates. 18 vols. Philad. 1798.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Erasmus, 84, F. Adagiorum Opus Des. Erasmi, Roterodami, ex postrema Autoris recognitione. Lugduni, 1550.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gibbon, 22, Q. Miscellaneous Works of Edward Gibbon, Esq. with Memoirs of his Life and Writings, composed by himself; illustrated from his Letters, with occasional Motes and Narratives, by John Lord Sheffield. 2 vols. London, 1796.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Golnitzius, 69, D. Abrah. Gölnitzii Dantisc. Ulysses Belgico-Gallicus, fidus tibi Dux et Achates, per Belgium Hispan. Regnum Galliæ, Ducat. Sabandiae, Turinum usque Pedemontii Metropolin. Lugduni Batavorum, 1631.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Great British, Tour through, &c. 16, D. A Tour through the whole Island of Great British, the Isles of Wight, Scilly, and other English and Scottish Isles of most Note. Interspersed with useful Observations, &c. &c. 4 vols. (Vol. III. wanting.) London, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grotius, 57, D. Hugonis Grotii quaedam hactenus inedita, aliaque ex Belgicè editis Latinê versa, Argumenti Theologici, Juridici, Politici. Amstelodami, apud Elzevirium, 1652.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Grunerus, 302, O. Jo. Frider. Gruneri, A. M. introductio in Antiquitates Romanas, qua Populi Romani Res publicae et privatae tam sub Republica libera quam sub Imperatoribus studiose explicantur. Jenae, 1746.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Gundlingius, 145—2, Q. N. H. Gundlingii Icti et Antecessoris in Acad. Fred. celeb. C. Trebatius Testa Ictus ab injuriis vet. atque recent. Scriptorum liberatus, cum Notis &c. &c. G. A. Jenichen. Lipsiae, 1736.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hales, 248, O. Statical Essays: containing Vegetable Staticks; or an Account of some Statical Experiments on the Sap in Vegetables, Haemastatics, &c. &c. &c. Stephen Hales, D. D. F. R. S. &c. 2 vols. London, 1738.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hales, 136, O. A Description of Ventilators: whereby grea quantities of Fresh Ai:r may with case be conveyed into Mines, Gaols, Hospitals, Work-houses, and Ships, in exchange for their Noxious Air, &c. &c- &c, Which was read before the Royal Society in May, 1741. By Stephen Hales, D. D. F. R. S. &c. Plates. London, 1743.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Harris, 21, F. Navigantium atque Itinerantium Bibliotheca; or, a complete collection of Voyages and Travels. Consisting of above six hundred of the most Authentic Writers, &c. &c. &c. With Charts, Maps, and Cuts, an introduction, &c. &c. Originally published by John Harris, D. D. & F. R. S. Now carefully revised, with large Additions, &c. &c 2 vols. London, 1748.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Heidfeldius, 234, O. Sphinx Theologico-Philosophica; promens ac proponens pia, erudita, arguta ac festiva aenigmata sive scrupos, ex variis &c. etc. authoribus sedulo comportatos, &c. &c, &c. Authori Johanne Heidfeldio. Herbornæae, 1631.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Hughes 42, F. The Natural History of Barbardoes. By the Rev. Griffith Hughes, A. M. F. R. S. Plates. Lond. 1750.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Keysler, 179, O. Travels through Germany, Bohemia, Hungary, Switzerland, Italy, and Lorrain. Giving a Description of the present State of those Countries, &c. &c. &c. By John George Keysler, F. R. S. Translated from the German. Plates. 4 vols. London, 1760.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Knox, 64 O. Leberal Education: or, a practical Greatise on the Methods of acquiring useful and polite Learning, &c.—By Vicesimus Knox, M. A. &c. Vol. II. Lond. 1789.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>La Chausse, 65, F. Romanum Museum, sive Thesaurus Eruditæ Antiquitatis, in quo proponuntur ac dilucidantur Gemmae, Idola, Insignia Sacerdotalia, Lucernae, Vasa, Bullae, Armillae, Fibulae, Claves, Annuli, Tesserae, Styli, Strigiles, Gatti, Phialae lacrymatoriae, Instrumenta Musica, Vota, Signa Militaria, Marmora, &c. &c. &c. Opera, et et studio Michaelis Angeli Causei de la Chausse. Cum permultis figuris. Tom. 2. Romae.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lamarck, 207, O. Flore Françoise ou Description Succincte de toutes les Plantes qui croissent naturellement en France, disposée selon une nouvelle méthode d&apos;Analyse, et à laquelle ou a joint la citation de leurs vertus les moins équivoques en Medecine, et de leur utilité dans les Arts. Par M. le Chevalier de Lamarck. Avec figures. 3 tom. A Paris, 1778.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Le Brun, 1, F. La Grande Galerie de Versailles, et les deux Salons qui l&apos;accompagnent, peints par Charles Le Brun, premier Peintre de Louis XIV. dessinés par Jean-Baptiste Massé, Peintre et Conseiller, &c. et gravés sous ses yeux par les meilleurs Mâitres du tems. A Paris, 1752.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lettsom, 43, O. The Naturalist’s and Traveller’s Companion, by Dr. Lettsom. London.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Linnæus 181, O. Caroli Linnaei species Plantarum, exhibentes Plantas rite cognitas, ad Genera relatas, cum Differentiis specificis, Nominibus trivialibus, Synonymis selectis, Locis natalibus, secundum Systema sexuale digestas.- Tom 2. Holmiae, 1762.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Linnæus 208, O. Caroli a Linné Equitis Systema Vegetabilium secundum Classes, Ordines, Genera, species, cum Characteribus et Differentiis. Curante Jo. Andrea Murray.  Parisiis, 1798.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Linnaeus, 111, O. Caroli Linnaei Amoenitates Academicae, seu Dissertationes variae Physicæ, Medicæ, Botanicæ, antehac seorsim editae, nunc, collectae et auctae cum tabulis. Accedit Hypothesis nova de Febrium intermittentium causa. Tom. 6. Lugduni Batavorum, 1749.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Locke, 103, F. The Works of John Locke. Portrait. 3 vols. London, 1714.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Lubersac, 55, F. Discours sur les Monumens Publics de tous les Ages et de tous les Peuples connus, suivi d’une description de Monument projeté à la gloire de Louis XVI. et de la France. Terminé par quelques Observations sur les principaux Monumens modernes de la ville de Paris, et plusieurs Projets de décoration et d&apos;utilité publique pour cette Capitale. Par M. l&apos;Abbé de Lubersac. A Paris, 1775.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mauners and Principles, &c. 193, O. An Estimate of the Manners and Principles of the Times. By the Author of Essays on the Characterstics, &c. 2 vols. London, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Marie, 53—3, O. Case of Jane Marie. Philadelphia, 1808.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Michaux, 1, O. Oaks of the United States and of Canada, by F. Andrew Michaux. Plates. Paris.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Mirabaud, 2, D. System of Nature; or the Laws of the Moral and Physical World. Translated from the French of M. Mirabaud. 2 vols. Philadelphia, 1808. (Presented by R. De Silver.)</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Nettleton, 253, O. A Treatise on Virtue and Happiness. By Thomas Nettleton, M. D. F. R. S. London, 1751.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Palmer, 81, Q. The General History of Printing, from its first Invention in the City of Mentz, to its first progress, &c. through the most celebrated Cities in Europe. Particularly its Introduction, Rise, and Progress, in England. The Center of the most Celebrated Printers, from the first Invention to 1520 and 1550. With an Account of their Works, &c. &c. By S. Palmer, Printer. London, 1732.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Philosophical Transactions, 83, Q. The Philosological Transactions and Collections to the year 1750. abridged and disposed under general heads. By Lowthorp, Jones, Eames and Martyn. 13 vols. Plates. London, 1721—1756.—Philosophical Transactions (at large,) giving some Account of the Present Undertaking, Studies, and  Labours of the Ingenious in many considerable parts of the World, from 1751 to 1761. Plato. 10 vols. London, 1753—1762. In all 23 vols.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pitiscus, 28, F. Lexicon Antiquitatum Romanarum, in quo Ritus et Antiquitates tum Graecis ac Romanis communes, tum Romanis peculiares, sacrae et profanae, publicae et privatae civiles ac Militares exponuntur, &c. &e. Auctore Samuele Pitisco: cum figuris in aes incisis.—Tom. 2. Leovardiæ, 1713.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pliny, 288. O. An address of thanks to a Good Prince, presented in the Panegyrick of Pliny upon Trajan, the Best of Roman Emperors. London, 1686.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pluche, 25, D. Spectacle de la Nature; or Nature delineated. Translated from the French of the Abbé Pluche. Plates 7 vols. (Vols. I. and II. wanting.) London, 1744.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Pontoppidaan, 60, F. The Natural History of Norway: containing an Account of the Temperature of the Air, the different Soils, Waters, Vegetables, Metals, Mineral. Beasts, Birds and Fishes, &c. &c. Interspersed with Physiological Notes, &c. &c. Translated from the Danish of the Rt. Rev. Erich Pontoppidan, Bishop of Bergen, &c. &c. With a Map and Plates. London, 1755.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Potter, 274, O. Archaeologia Græca: or, the Antiquities of Greece. By John Potter, M. A. &c. 2 vols. Oxford, 1697.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Raius, 53, F. Historia Plantarum, species hactenus editas aliasque insuper multas noviter inventas et descriptas complectens, &c. &c. &c. Auctore Joanne Raio, F. R. S., &c. Tom. 2. Londini, 1686.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rapinus, 328, O. Renati Rapini Soc. Jesu, Hortorum libri IV. cum disputatione de Cultura Hortensi. Joan. Meursii Fil. Arboretum sacrum. Angeli Politiani Rusticus. Adhaec Lipsii Leges Hortenses, et Lazari Bonamici. carmen de Vita Rustica. Ultrajecti, 1672.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Reaumur, 44, Q. Memoires pour servir a l&apos;Histoire des Insectes. Par M. de Reaumur, de l&apos;Académie Royale de Sciences. Avec plusieurs figures. 6 tom. A Paris, 1734—1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Rousseau, 26, D. Emilius & Sophia: or, a New System of Education. Translated from the French of J. J. Rousseau. 4 vols. London, 1783.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Schottus, 39, D. Itinerarium Italiae, Rerumque Romanarum Libri tres: A Francisco Schotto editi, et ab Hieronymo Capugnano aucti, &c. Antverpiae, 1625.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Sheridan 119, O. British Education: or, the source of the Disorders of Great Britain, &c. &c. &c. By Thomas  Sjeridan, A. M. London, 1756.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Smetius, 118, Q. Antiquitates Neomagenses. Sive Notitia Rarissimarum Rerum Antiquarum, quas in vetere Batavorum Oppido studiose comparavit Johannes Smetius, Pater et Filius, &c. &c Cum figuris. Noviomagi Batavorum, 1678.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Soulavie, 237, O. Histoire Naturelle de la France Meridionale, par M. l&apos;Abbé Giraud Soulavie. Avec Planches. 7 tom. A Nismes, 1780—1782.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Swammerdam, 17, F. The Book of Nature; or, the History of Insects; reduced to distinct Classes, confirmed by particular Instances, displayed in the Anatomical Analysis of many species, and lllustrated with copperplates, &c. &c. &c. By John Swammerdam, M. D.; with the Life of the Author, by H. Boerhaave, M. D. Translated from the Dutch and Latin by Thomas Flloyd. Revised and improved by Notes from Reaumur and others, by John Hill, M. D. London, 1758.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Temple, 109, F. The Works of Sir William Temple, Baronet. With an Account of the Life and Writings of the Author. 2 vols. London, 1720.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Temple,  271, O. Miscellanea. Essays, by Sir William Temple, Baronet. Parts II. and III. London, 1691—1701.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Topsel, 83, F. The History of Four footed Beasts and Serpents, &c. &c. Collected out of the Writings of Conradus Gesner and other Authors, by Edward Topsel. To which is added, the Theater of Insects, &c. by T Muffet, Dr. of Physick. With many cuts. Lond. 1658.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Turnbul 239, O. Observations upon Liberal Education, in all its Branches, &c. &c. &c. By George Turnbull, LL. D. London, 1742.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Vertot, 225, O. Vertot’s Miscellanies; consisting of Dissertations, I. On the true Original of the French, &c. II. on the Salique Laws. III. On the Sainte Ampoulle, &c. IV. On the ancient forms of Oaths used among the French. V. On the ancient Burial places of the Kings of France, by the R. F. Mabillon. VI. On the time of the Nativity of Christ discovered from ancient Medals, by M. Vaillant. Translated from the French by John Henley, M. A. London, 1723.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Virgil, 36, D. The Works of Virgil: translated into English blank verse, with explanatory Notes and Critical Observations. By Joseph Trapp, D. D. Vols. I. and III. London, 1731.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Voyages and Travels, &c. 25, Q. A New General Collection of Voyages and Travels; consisting of the most Esteemed Relations, which have been hitherto published in any Language: comprehending every thing remarkable in its kind, in Europe, Asia, Africa, and America, &c. &c. Maps and Plates. 4 vols. London, 1745.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Washington, 51—1, O. Washington on Husbandry. Alexandria, 1803.</TITLE>
  </row>
  <row>
    <OCLC></OCLC>
    <TITLE>Xenophon, 192, O. Cyropædia; or, the Institutions of Cyrus. By Xenophon. Translated from the Greek by the Hon. Maurice Ashley, Esq. 2 vols. London, 1728.</TITLE>
  </row>
</root>
